<programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221119230000 +0000" stop="20221120015000 +0000" catchup-id="lwNuPSVZN4lWqrue8hcwxCO3crim3Dxaf0iZK0Br"><title>Apocalypse Now: Final Cut</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Powerful, controversial Vietnam War epic. Assigned to seek out and execute a deranged war hero, who has set up a brutal dictatorship deep in the jungle, a battle-fatigued captain embarks on a harrowing, surreal odyssey through the war-torn jungle, where human values have become debased and have been replaced by paranoia, schizophrenia, violence and nihilism. Inspired by Joseph Conrad's novel Heart of Darkness. Winner of the Academy Award for Best Cinematography, and Oscar, Golden Globe and BAFTA nominations for Best Motion Picture.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221120015000 +0000" stop="20221120032000 +0000" catchup-id="XfAFQUvLVcgL2o_G5kqU2DpO20VRsq80DI0NRcve"><title>The People's Piazza: A History of Covent Garden</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>David Olusoga tells the story of London's Covent Garden Piazza. Helped by experts and eyewitnesses, he conjures up ghosts of the past - market traders, sex workers and activists.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221120032000 +0000" stop="20221120060500 +0000" catchup-id="LCZO82TMyHQYVKZsUnUuswUwQ69jZHpr3RGWgB9t"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221120060500 +0000" stop="20221120070000 +0000" catchup-id="IIvUU5ygO9db1QRbUHF8lO4pdFjrnaaHvTmnb-ua"><title>Countryfile : Mount Edgcumbe Country Park</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/OmIgbtzITYU0rcuGfMFGUg.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221120070000 +0000" stop="20221120073000 +0000" catchup-id="iifLjbTRD7t7y70O6mK0YQExj5qYr8ibnn5AwBDv"><title>Landward</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/u3Db7sHjg7elQb5gbijcKg.jpg"></icon><desc>In this episode, Dougie visits a farm near Beauly that is taking a regenerative approach to livestock farming. He meets a couple inspired by time spent in Kenya, who move their sheep and cattle around the land regularly to graze. Elsewhere, Anne is in a forest in South Lanarkshire where she gets to grips with the ancient woodland skill of coppicing, and Rosie makes an early start to count pink-footed geese taking off at Montrose Basin. And now the sheep shearing season is over, Cammy tries his hand at goat shearing.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221120073000 +0000" stop="20221120080000 +0000" catchup-id="d1v0gf_hnIzJ3O1hDlaVioFcHoOKlOwvdTg4KUcL"><title>Beechgrove Gardens in Winter</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Carole Baxter and Diana Yates are at Beechgrove to demonstrate just what needs to be done for autumn and winter. They show how to plant garlic and take a look at some great species to plant for colourful barks and stems. There is also pruning to be getting on with, with the garden’s buddleia getting some attention, and there is some great advice on caring for heathers. George Anderson is in his garden pruning hydrangea, and Brian Cunningham is lifting the gladioli he planted earlier in the summer. Plus the usual round-up of handy hints and tips for the week ahead.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221120080000 +0000" stop="20221120090000 +0000" catchup-id="ioqXDr2tv2OQ_BiITgfcCd7J8DvqBxI5FJHz25p1"><title>Weatherman Walking : Weatherman Walking for Children in Need</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Derek Brockway gets walking for Children in Need. On a nine-mile hike between Wrexham and Hope Mountain, he meets local people and explores the landscape. He also learns about some of the projects that are supported by Children in Need all over Wales. There’s a challenge, too: Derek wants Pudsey to show off some top dance moves at a celebratory party on top of the mountain at the end of the walk, but Pudsey’s repertoire is limited to waving and doing ‘thumbs up’. Dance phenomenon the Matsena Brothers are called in to help, but can they teach Pudsey the moves in time?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221120090000 +0000" stop="20221120100000 +0000" catchup-id="k9E7OS2J3bQibhKBBIRK-X06tJ7tdzr6y6rzNYBg"><title>This Farming Life</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/Ze4YmpYL_uzFB0C4cNvB_w.jpg"></icon><desc>Autumn is on the way in Loch Ness, and at Corrimony Farm, David and Barbara are embracing a new piece of tech that involves fitting GPS collars to their herd of stabiliser cows so that they can roam the rough upland grazing high in the hills above their farm. Late summer is a busy time for Barbara and her sustainable cut flower business, and she hosts the first of many sunflower tea events in the barn. Further down the glen, it’s all quiet on the Frasers' farm. The whole family have come down with Covid, and Joanna makes a lifechanging career decision. In Orkney, ten-year-old Harvey is preparing to sell his fat lambs at the mart. Later, as Sean is moving cattle with dad Michael and uncle Martin, his top dog, Tara, collapses. And in Stranraer, weeks behind schedule, the pasteuriser finally arrives on site. Meanwhile, Andy and the family register their new Clydesdale foals.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221120100000 +0000" stop="20221120113000 +0000" catchup-id="Z0GhcCuD9tW9OCmxiYYmXqiYgETYKB3cYQzNQEr5"><title>Saturday Kitchen Best Bites</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/RP_5PKqX4rIMk-YZUlBkXg.jpg"></icon><desc>Matt Tebbutt takes a look back at some of his favourite recipes and best moments from Saturday Kitchen.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221120113000 +0000" stop="20221120123000 +0000" catchup-id="kefz4UkKqnkYGceTrVMJTGjFVMCZIHVSs4sT_1yZ"><title>Mary Berry's Country House Secrets : Highclere Castle</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/z8rDp7vAi9VDWxlG--6PPA.jpg"></icon><desc>Four-part series in which Mary Berry discovers the rich history of the nation's greatest stately homes. In this programme, she visits Highclere Castle, home to the eighth Earl and Countess of Carnarvon and renowned as the setting for some of the most lavish and influential weekend house parties in history. Mary discovers what it takes to keep a home like this going in today's world, meeting everyone from the family to the house staff and the estate's gamekeepers. Inspired by what she discovers, Mary creates a delicious spread in the estate's kitchen, including raspberry tartlets, gamekeeper's stew and an elaborate menu for a grand finale dinner</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221120123000 +0000" stop="20221120130000 +0000" catchup-id="jydDbZhPY3PWEzuqqwnBSGt4UNup6VmJAMAqstGf"><title>Recipes That Made Me : Kashmir</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Restaurateur Nisha Katona travels around the UK meeting home cooks to discover family recipes passed down through generations from across the Indian subcontinent. In this episode, Nisha travels to Yorkshire to meet families with connections to the Himalayan region of Kashmir. Kashmiri food has little exposure in this country and Nisha wants to discover all she can about it.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221120130000 +0000" stop="20221120171500 +0000" catchup-id="EX7Rv_Aqtcr4i5TJi4yA3nq-Dg_L9dZa4gZIYvs-"><title>Snooker: UK Championship : Final - Part One</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/nB-Jl81WWFm5aK1-SO57Wg.jpg"></icon><desc>Live coverage of the first part of the final at the Barbican Centre in York.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221120171500 +0000" stop="20221120181500 +0000" catchup-id="ZNiymG0NiuJ1kXaq4IfmomYuV_9wAEEnW0w4SNWz"><title>This Farming Life</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/Ze4YmpYL_uzFB0C4cNvB_w.jpg"></icon><desc>Summer turns to autumn in Bute, Emma and Ewan are in the market for new tups or rams to produce good prime lambs the following spring. When they arrive at Kelso, the biggest sheep market in Europe, one pen in particular catches that their eye belongs to none other than Mike from Collessie Farm in Fife. Prices are high, but they can’t afford to come away empty-handed. Later in Fife, Mike puts in a shift at the family’s feed business, delivering animal feed to customers all over Fife. Meanwhile, in Orkney, Sean’s dad is preparing to drive hundreds of miles with his tups to one of the last sales of the year in Carlisle. It’s the Autumn Equinox, and the ferry crossing is rough. Back home, Sean has figured out a new way to sell from the island, joining the 52 per cent of farmers now buying and selling online.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221120181500 +0000" stop="20221120190000 +0000" catchup-id="qflhcHX5yJCuFCnmu2v3rgMivmGALl5RXyoemYpG"><title>Golf: World Tour Highlights</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The top golfers on the European Tour battle it out in the final tournament of the season.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221120190000 +0000" stop="20221120220000 +0000" catchup-id="T3K9HxhqyJ9cZZSzDdgCW3XD5JM5tJUzWgJGXLFq"><title>Snooker: UK Championship : Final - Part Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/nB-Jl81WWFm5aK1-SO57Wg.jpg"></icon><desc>Live coverage of the concluding part of the final at the Barbican Centre in York.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221120220000 +0000" stop="20221120220200 +0000" catchup-id="ptv2x4UdBXCofPaMDrDLiFAXDF4DVaO-oqW6OS8B"><title>Introduction to Surge</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221120220200 +0000" stop="20221120233500 +0000" catchup-id="fDTjtT0IRimcFeyQXcUDlfxRdtFkFz4j1nAdEI7F"><title>Surge</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/0r-XLKfkWz38Z6B9JonnTA.jpg"></icon><desc>Airport security worker Joseph lives a mundane existence with a daily commute and a repetitive job. After a frustrating reunion with his unresponsive parents, he cracks under the pressure and embarks on a frenzy of emotional release.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221120233500 +0000" stop="20221120234500 +0000" catchup-id="zXFMk07SN8vgFuxJ5fa0V1feZl5kl7rQOt3kCYm5"><title>Precious Hair and Beauty</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>An ode to the mundanity and madness of the high street, told through the window of an African hair salon.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221120234500 +0000" stop="20221121004500 +0000" catchup-id="O3gpyuhcrvXNYXQpCajC4Ux3_kIGLFaP8k_W5ycj"><title>Hong Kong's Fight for Freedom</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>In 2019, the Hong Kong government proposes a law allowing suspects to be extradited to China. The bill sparks a wave of anger across the city as people fear Hong Kong’s autonomy from mainland China is under threat. Using groundbreaking artificial intelligence to protect the identities of the protesters, this film tells the story of four young Hongkongers who join mass protests across the city and feel increasingly disillusioned by the government’s response. They soon find themselves drawn into a cycle of violence that threatens to tear the city apart.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121004500 +0000" stop="20221121014500 +0000" catchup-id="367g2RUmNeQsrSlNa7mFKaurq4-tzzXSxzrv_r8p"><title>Signed: DIY SOS : The Big Build for Children in Need</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/xx_ksbJlAVaVwOqLcDUy7g.jpg"></icon><desc>In this Children in Need Special, the DIY SOS team joins forces with Radio 2. Their mission is to transform a derelict site into a safe base for a young women’s charity in Leeds.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121014500 +0000" stop="20221121024500 +0000" catchup-id="WUPVb3U_q7BIvDhdcA8hxp0PSXfx9beOXpyQrTaK"><title>Signed: Question Time</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/QsmtxqlGZlxjGLxPYGJ_4w.jpg"></icon><desc>Fiona Bruce presents an hour of debate from Snape in Suffolk. On the panel: from the government, Victoria Atkins MP, financial secretary to the Treasury; Labour’s Jonathan Ashworth MP, who shadows the Department of Work and Pensions; Ian Blackford MP, the Scottish National Party’s Westminster leader; economics editor at the Spectator magazine, Kate Andrews; and broadcaster, columnist and former chair of the Equality and Human Rights Commission, Sir Trevor Phillips.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121024500 +0000" stop="20221121035000 +0000" catchup-id="P-Oq6NhH89WtwMNtcogVAf_MDhqptFe13ejUAvci"><title>Signed: Ambulance</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/JbsgWPK_AY6vsONGYecFWA.jpg"></icon><desc>It’s payday weekend and the start of a busy night shift for crews across Durham and Darlington. Sixty-five patients are waiting for an ambulance, and control are already answering one new call every 20 seconds. Crewmates Nicola and Claire attend to a man who has been found unresponsive on the roadside, then are immediately dispatched to a known regular caller who is feeling suicidal. However, when they arrive at the patient’s house, she is nowhere to be seen. When they locate her, the patient refuses to go to hospital, but the crew believe she needs further support, so they attempt to navigate the complexities of out-of-hours mental health services. Becky and Chloe must care for a male patient experiencing epileptic fits. As they transport him to hospital, he begins vomiting and becomes less responsive. For Becky, the job feels all too close to home as she recalls growing up with a father who suffered from frequent seizures.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121035000 +0000" stop="20221121063000 +0000" catchup-id="UTrzQxU8O81kWaJBPnfY9oEeO0MWCrH7wkzr7vfL"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121063000 +0000" stop="20221121071500 +0000" catchup-id="MEc6Zkgsu7bxbO3W5qoTycGB5Sr0SNuslQeoFwZn"><title>Bargain Hunt : Children in Need Special</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/_n4I9rQNXfb1yt_rdabD_Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Christina Trevanion presents a children’s TV special programme to raise money for BBC Children in Need. Masters of Saturday morning mayhem Dick and Dom take on 1980s Blue Peter presenter Mark Curry and Newsround’s De-Graft Mensah. Experts Philip Serrell and Roo Irvine guide the celebrity teams as they search for bargains at Southwell Antiques Fair. Who will make the most profits for Pudsey when their buys go under the hammer with auctioneer Charles Hanson?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121071500 +0000" stop="20221121080000 +0000" catchup-id="sXwfs3zdbQOFWXxhRO5fpmdJwklYCgt5WwgA7Ugk"><title>The Repair Shop</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/nNgi6NKnt4-BVyFPrYGWJQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Jay Blades and the team restore a musical grenadier guard doll, a navigational sextant and a wooden chest from Sri Lanka.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121080000 +0000" stop="20221121090000 +0000" catchup-id="Hpii28irhSM6UZBcxBAFVRDBtO5V8fCKplNIZxma"><title>Signed: MasterChef: The Professionals</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/9iEXf-1bVLUoRAvPsDSWxA.jpg"></icon><desc>Four new chefs begin their bid for the coveted MasterChef: The Professionals title as they compete in two challenges set by judges Anna Haugh and Marcus Wareing. Only the strongest two chefs will go through to the quarter-final. The first two chefs face a Skills Test devised by Marcus. He asks them to make ravioli with a cheese and ‘nduja filling, served with an oregano butter emulsion. Who will have the cookery knowledge and control to plate up a dish full of flavour in just 20 minutes, and who will fold under the pressure? Anna sets the test for the other two chefs, who must fillet a rainbow trout, cook a portion and serve it with a pea and wild garlic puree. Then the four contenders have a final chance to impress as they cook a two-course Signature Menu. Now is their time to shine with dishes they have designed and practiced.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121090000 +0000" stop="20221121100000 +0000" catchup-id="CNm3WRvpAnLmW2aoJFILm7wHTX-T0ZErWWMP3q7m"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/O4C25N7vCNk5hoXbwDrnIw.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest headlines, breaking news and sport from the BBC newsroom.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121100000 +0000" stop="20221121113000 +0000" catchup-id="vvqfpuD9us62FSt3tHpSwXHiakNivpaKGJLv4YB5"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/O4C25N7vCNk5hoXbwDrnIw.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121113000 +0000" stop="20221121121500 +0000" catchup-id="gpEjtdBZd40HLBiZpLfn9PGoCUAxp2d47AmGqXpE"><title>Bargain Hunt : Westpoint 9</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/_n4I9rQNXfb1yt_rdabD_Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Join Natasha Raskin Sharp for today's Bargain Hunt from Exeter's Westpoint Arena. Experts Philip Serrell and Catherine Southon try to help the teams make a profit when they head to auction. Natasha also pops down to Exeter's Historic quayside to find out why it was once one of the busiest trading centres in England.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121121500 +0000" stop="20221121130000 +0000" catchup-id="5GGY_9qv7cdTIqNd0BhlT5cBhiv6M2fxZQ84NlVG"><title>Politics Live</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The big political issues of the day.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121130000 +0000" stop="20221121134500 +0000" catchup-id="AV0aGd0wRl2C6RBd7rpWGxiY6zZQoVyRCKjCSUiN"><title>Best House in Town : Leicester: Detached</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/Pyk0kvy9AYicOqXjF8JDiw.jpg"></icon><desc>Homeowners compete in the hope of being judged to have the best house in town. Today, three detached homes in Leicestershire - a retro-style family home, a country-style new build and a house with some seriously modern twists.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121134500 +0000" stop="20221121141500 +0000" catchup-id="fP5TASkVMhGmvWFluL-Z2ADFvkXMDBdkaaQ-AZOl"><title>Eggheads</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/kxjywN32Sf7ZLWFid1pwVQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Jeremy Vine hosts the show where every day a new team of challengers take on probably the greatest quiz team in Britain. Can the challengers triumph or will the cash prize roll over to the next show?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121141500 +0000" stop="20221121144500 +0000" catchup-id="kQwhxDHqj6jvTFPBYBVvZpOBIHg7LbaZcDnETpe0"><title>Lightning</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/O9yEJFaPlaRcdU7dXdvZEg.jpg"></icon><desc>Comedian Zoe Lyons presents the electrifyingly fast quiz with a £3,000 jackpot. Six plucky contestants compete across six rounds testing their general knowledge, quick thinking and speedy reactions whilst our ruthless spotlight patrols the studio. The contestants’ motivation in each round is simple: stay out of the light and you’ll be all right!</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121144500 +0000" stop="20221121151500 +0000" catchup-id="xBy7-cmelOfQFhdkzZIzERwukO5_wvT_zxQbUFjp"><title>Fish Town</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/A3KxsSlg81R09sW1uc7BbA.jpg"></icon><desc>Six-part series about the UK's biggest fishing port, Peterhead. The Reliance heads to a fishing ground off the Shetland Isles in search of whitefish and prawns.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121151500 +0000" stop="20221121161500 +0000" catchup-id="RjxOegTfO5HFrgmC0poWfoejA_RqEhBvYHRQtk6F"><title>The Great British Sewing Bee</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/fIKz7V4GhllGHXD42WedGA.jpg"></icon><desc>Joe Lycett is back in charge, with twelve of Britain's most talented home sewers competing to win one of TV's toughest creative challenges. Judges Patrick Grant and Esme Young cast an expert eye over the garments, in the contest to find Britain's best amateur sewer. Week One sees Patrick and Esme settling the contestants in with a trio of challenges based on everyday wardrobe staples. They start with their first Pattern Challenge, creating the simple, clean lines of the versatile classic sleeveless blouse known as a shell top. For the Transformation Challenge, the sewers must turn old T-shirts into completely new garments for men, women or children, in just 90 minutes. And in the Made to Measure, mannequins are replaced with real-life models. Who will whip up a well-fitting buffet dress and win themselves Garment of the Week, and whose hopes of staying in the competition will flounder?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121161500 +0000" stop="20221121171500 +0000" catchup-id="19wwJMEb4HDL7x-Li3VlHFszJRA7hfGL3Gj_qPDe"><title>Natural World : Nature's Perfect Partners</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/MCjYbjwCVN7wlVqpak936w.jpg"></icon><desc>In the animal kingdom, what do you do if you've got an itch you can't scratch, food you can't get your teeth into or you simply need some home security? Well, you find yourself a partner - and not necessarily someone like you! Hippos are joining forces with fish for a full-body exfoliation. Ravens are inviting wolverines to dinner for some bone-crunching assistance. Bill Bailey introduces these and so many more extraordinary partnerships found in nature.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121171500 +0000" stop="20221121180000 +0000" catchup-id="mDbjMwLbirkxAdujOfQJcOVHZ5EH-37v4s-RNpgX"><title>Flog It! : Bristol Cathedral 21</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121180000 +0000" stop="20221121183000 +0000" catchup-id="mkOgOHlugWKMFMSZrXzrzgLptkXoIwugR5a_G1Xn"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games : Week 12: Monday</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/QTvvZ81udNlpPp2OS-TMAQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Every day this week, former winners Maggie Aderin-Pocock, Cariad Lloyd, Gareth Malone and Mike Wozniak take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Facing their second chance to win a prize, will the winning stars opt for the House of Games golden goblets, or will they be tempted with the must-have House of Games golden fondue set?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121183000 +0000" stop="20221121190000 +0000" catchup-id="1TeczblytqkCt-ca2KNvsl_KRDei2zsD5_-QIeSV"><title>Strictly It Takes Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/jBI3R8x1LdHWuBnckASH_A.jpg"></icon><desc>Rylan chats exclusively to the latest couple to be eliminated from the competition. Plus more interviews and backstage gossip from some of the remaining couples.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121190000 +0000" stop="20221121193000 +0000" catchup-id="1Avy3wdhU0_4Incub1UBFuwCVZ84dXT517In1OhQ"><title>Iolo's Anglesey</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Iolo heads out to sea to look for Risso’s dolphins. Underwater, an artificial reef has formed from an old shipwreck. He finds roosting bats at an old priory, and dragonflies and beautiful rare plants on Anglesey’s fens. On the Alaw estuary, he gets a rare sight of Britain’s smallest bird of prey, the merlin, as well as Brent geese overwintering on Anglesey.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121193000 +0000" stop="20221121200000 +0000" catchup-id="IbrdYK7icaTpD1qjKrWPj0K3wV-EK3ya6fBLkZAp"><title>Mastermind</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/2x2bAg5oZd-Vt9Cw9pfaCw.jpg"></icon><desc>Clive Myrie tests four more contenders on their specialist subjects and general knowledge in the tenth heat of the series. The specialist subjects are the life of Anne Lister, Dear Evan Hansen, Elizabeth I and the feature films of David Lynch.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121200000 +0000" stop="20221121203000 +0000" catchup-id="vlGYKDo9b5HgNZJ64WWjyP6c3ZxZv8Ia7tvs5d-C"><title>Only Connect : Jillies v Morporkians</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/-dwHFg_l7ZoJCCwKGGBPXQ.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121203000 +0000" stop="20221121210000 +0000" catchup-id="RhB1Vu0n9AdNFpNyO7o6odPwllmtpf6qnCHa75RM"><title>University Challenge</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/DthQg2qIu4T3wO2ltne1Hg.jpg"></icon><desc>It's the penultimate match of the first round. Newnham College, Cambridge, face the Courtauld Institute of Art for a place in the second round. Jeremy Paxman asks the questions.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121210000 +0000" stop="20221121220000 +0000" catchup-id="tNItqjFRIdgQS_Rx1uOqghg9rNU_yMxl6bou6CbF"><title>Hong Kong's Fight for Freedom</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>In October 2019, as Beijing celebrates 70 years of the People’s Republic of China, Hong Kong is being torn apart by violent protests. Using groundbreaking artificial intelligence to protect the identities of the protesters, this film tells the story of four young people locked in a brutal battle with the authorities to defend their way of life. As the police response turns deadly, the protesters respond with violence of their own. Families turn against each other, and the city is brought to its knees, but the protesters feel they are fighting for their freedom and refuse to give in. Holed up in a university campus, surrounded by police and with little response from the government, the protesters make their final stand. Meanwhile, Beijing is preparing a crackdown that will change the face of Hong Kong forever.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121220000 +0000" stop="20221121223000 +0000" catchup-id="4tMn6QRNOYyJI-ybMCiZgsbxQ4rJ-w668UKNhYy2"><title>Motherland : Mother's Day</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/FvFPBxUeXtLDcPgWOyy_BA.jpg"></icon><desc>Mother's Day leaves Julia feeling ignored while Meg gets spoilt rotten. Amanda endures a passive aggressive lunch with her appalling mother Felicity.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121223000 +0000" stop="20221121231500 +0000" catchup-id="vLVWzB9aqOlIEowhVaqFK-lG0uRThglnYQLzgZ4-"><title>Newsnight</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bUQ-JbBOx1dTvpjQEinXPw.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Victoria Derbyshire.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221121231500 +0000" stop="20221122010000 +0000" catchup-id="oktej-mYdP8yKEI6yqdy_Dtx_4lZX9ifXOfRVBhl"><title>Pawn Sacrifice</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/rgAVubLAuerH0Y5Qhg7kNQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Biographical drama. Growing up in Brooklyn, the son of an expatriot Russian single mother Bobby Fischer lives for chess, winning all his junior matches. His dreams are of being the youngest ever world champion. To do this, he needs to beat the Russian masters and his own increasing paranoia.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122010000 +0000" stop="20221122020000 +0000" catchup-id="-HwhvEkGub8V9Qb7SDSCLhoFQJfHqCwRhX-_uE0q"><title>Countryfile : Mount Edgcumbe Country Park</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/OmIgbtzITYU0rcuGfMFGUg.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122020000 +0000" stop="20221122031500 +0000" catchup-id="Nv9NmD8pW6u22_zijN1xsAo1jafrua53Yq_BZ1uh"><title>Signed: Autumnwatch</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/7dAJ_0aHHbx4b_-Ucah3tw.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122031500 +0000" stop="20221122041000 +0000" catchup-id="SS-QHpodUJdM3uwhodakuHoJKaAcVACw_2teJblV"><title>Signed: Unbreakable</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122041000 +0000" stop="20221122063000 +0000" catchup-id="vzp9gWWBf0znnKPRoCrCiQ9NLOVzXUX5w6QcUE8H"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122063000 +0000" stop="20221122071500 +0000" catchup-id="3FjV4GSrkRxN1dT_fWiP2jQmKfgaIUqEWJ-qzFkA"><title>The Travelling Auctioneers</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Christina and Will help a mother and daughter sift through family heirlooms. Some jewellery is worth an unexpected sum, and Will saves furniture from going to landfill.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122071500 +0000" stop="20221122080000 +0000" catchup-id="syuth9ne2NQESsSJ5jIhb6ryWDogW3ZRD6Hu5m6f"><title>Money for Nothing</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/7QssTsRrKA7Ad2b5d9jQFw.jpg"></icon><desc>Sarah Moore is in Buckinghamshire, determined to save quality items from ending up on the scrapheap at Beaconsfield recycling centre. She diverts a dressing table, a bamboo dining set and some beech tree leaves from the skips and enlists the help of screen-print designer Daniel Heath and upcycler Rachel Henderson to transform them. Will the team's hard work generate profits for the items' unsuspecting owners?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122080000 +0000" stop="20221122090000 +0000" catchup-id="4mVQKtw7AhjtrE3GUTfR6nuHGduV8Dt3RKwxer5P"><title>Signed: MasterChef: The Professionals</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/9iEXf-1bVLUoRAvPsDSWxA.jpg"></icon><desc>Today's skills tests involve butchering a saddle of rabbit and removing the meat from a crab. The four contenders then try to impress the judges with their signature dishes.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122090000 +0000" stop="20221122100000 +0000" catchup-id="XwnD2iK_7sLGFyFq9PQLyHNY9HbUrnQNC-ddBVsk"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/O4C25N7vCNk5hoXbwDrnIw.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest headlines, breaking news and sport from the BBC newsroom.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122100000 +0000" stop="20221122121500 +0000" catchup-id="HS54fIMDNc560sPcwIwT0KDEB13UpFZFiKMovQgs"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/O4C25N7vCNk5hoXbwDrnIw.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122121500 +0000" stop="20221122130000 +0000" catchup-id="1xXWV_PpHJLaY7laarfcFhHqjWhze-5-PDqkuqym"><title>Politics Live</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The big political issues of the day.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122130000 +0000" stop="20221122134500 +0000" catchup-id="mKPVHam8G1QKnYNhf7flPYSlOu5No50p5GySfRH0"><title>Best House in Town : Leicester: Terraced</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/Pyk0kvy9AYicOqXjF8JDiw.jpg"></icon><desc>The owners of three terraced houses in Leicester hand over their keys to a group of property-obsessed and knowledgeable ‘nosey neighbours’ who will be judging which property should go through to Friday's final. The judges look at a traditional Edwardian end-of-terrace, a Victorian terrace brought crashing into the 21st century and a terrace that’s been stretched to its limit.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122134500 +0000" stop="20221122141500 +0000" catchup-id="XfYDcGOymQ3MUtN7fxa3IO_eU7wzZ95FL9KDjiHf"><title>Eggheads</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/kxjywN32Sf7ZLWFid1pwVQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Jeremy Vine hosts the show where every day a new team of challengers take on probably the greatest quiz team in Britain. Can the challengers triumph or will the cash prize roll over to the next show?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122141500 +0000" stop="20221122144500 +0000" catchup-id="q3ix98B1hrGe52SFHRCjFp2SBofx8z1_fGb5f1mA"><title>Lightning</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/O9yEJFaPlaRcdU7dXdvZEg.jpg"></icon><desc>Comedian Zoe Lyons presents the electrifyingly fast quiz with a £3,000 jackpot.Six plucky contestants compete across six rounds testing their general knowledge, quick thinking and speedy reactions whilst our ruthless spotlight patrols the studio.The contestants' motivation in each round is simple: stay out of the light and you'll be alright!</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122144500 +0000" stop="20221122151500 +0000" catchup-id="Tkv1BDJjqttuoTaZzGr4pkzF95fLRDzPjp3V6m_T"><title>Fish Town</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/A3KxsSlg81R09sW1uc7BbA.jpg"></icon><desc>Series about the UK's biggest fishing port. In the remote Norwegian sector of the North Sea, the pair trawler Rosebloom gets a visit from a Norwegian coastguard boat.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122151500 +0000" stop="20221122161500 +0000" catchup-id="vyh1xHYptViRbKpkEBK47QLybzHV1yYILnycYp8T"><title>The Great British Sewing Bee : Summer Week</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/lcSJChXNgDU8MD5nEoKJ4Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Joe Lycett hosts as Summer Week hits the sewing room, with three challenges themed around sewing clothes to look and feel cool in even the fiercest heat. Patrick and Esme's Pattern Challenge is a pair of paperbag shorts. They might be a small garment, but creating the signature shape means perfecting pockets, tackling tricky turn-ups and wrestling an elastic waistband with a mind of its own. The sewers hit the beach in the Transformation, sculpting second-hand men's swimming gear into a woman's outfit worthy of sunset cocktails, all in just 90 minutes. Finally, button-down sun dresses are the focus of the Made to Measure. As well as style, fit and finish, the judges have their eagle eyes primed for perfectly aligned buttonholes and secure fastenings. Who will miss the mark and be the second sewer to leave the competition?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122161500 +0000" stop="20221122171500 +0000" catchup-id="6cJTNAB5N44uMf3u5FXk9Mp53e7UIe5yntCndLyP"><title>Flog It! : St Albans</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc>Flog It! comes from historic St Albans Cathedral and Abbey in Hertfordshire. Antique experts Claire Rawle and Jonathan Pratt find a selection of antiques and collectibles to take to auction. Claire discovers an arts and crafts bowl which may have belonged to George Bernard Shaw's wife, and Jonathan gets excited when he finds a drawing by the artist Dame Laura Knight. Paul Martin takes a trip underground as he explores the intriguing Royston cave which boasts medieval carvings.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122171500 +0000" stop="20221122180000 +0000" catchup-id="WMpmPCo8W3GZCGi0WoAW8bnHYjM2a_G03rBcA8gL"><title>Pointless</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/LpFQPFQIkafkjK47T0qzjg.jpg"></icon><desc>The quiz in which contestants try to score as few points as possible by plumbing the depths of their general knowledge to come up with the answers no-one else could think of. Presented by Alexander Armstrong and co-host Richard Osman.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122180000 +0000" stop="20221122183000 +0000" catchup-id="cTcGEuWQhwbd76a5sG71WCoX9orbwS2wxqd7VMj-"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games : Week 12: Tuesday</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/QTvvZ81udNlpPp2OS-TMAQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Every day this week, former winners Maggie Aderin-Pocock, Cariad Lloyd, Gareth Malone and Mike Wozniak take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Facing their second chance to win a prize, will the winning stars opt for the House of Games golden goblets, or will they be tempted with the must-have House of Games golden fondue set?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122183000 +0000" stop="20221122190000 +0000" catchup-id="YPvJPVYeQwUCHHOlP5VSfv5yVehQoBp_gGRwHBAi"><title>Strictly It Takes Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/jBI3R8x1LdHWuBnckASH_A.jpg"></icon><desc>Rylan is back with more backstage gossip and behind-the-scenes action from Strictly.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122190000 +0000" stop="20221122193000 +0000" catchup-id="pt8mLKaIR7Bj3R_RiYWyXg5yblz0l0tCPOWZ-gLL"><title>Between the Covers</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/8wf6Lq-RQXgwlOUeULrMyg.jpg"></icon><desc>Sara is joined by actor and author Paterson Joseph, newsreader Sophie Raworth, and comedians Al Murray and Jenny Eclair. They share their favourite books and review the two book club choices: the new book pick, Sometimes People Die by Simon Stephenson, and the selection from the Booker Prize backlist, The Long Song by Andrea Levy.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122193000 +0000" stop="20221122200000 +0000" catchup-id="Hmk9AvCkizamxJCBRLsaTB19V3-ftlOwXT6j2l1R"><title>EastEnders</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/AIA24J34rsuQZvF_cXzqeg.jpg"></icon><desc>As disaster strikes for Janine, Linda takes a big risk. Ben questions Lola’s approach to what’s going on, and Rocky tries to make things up to Kathy.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122200000 +0000" stop="20221122210000 +0000" catchup-id="Bzq36idah8_geSx9wEfYM4c0xB-4yT2bYcQdOBDG"><title>Celebrity Antiques Road Trip</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/5_Dul6Lg_CFLFmGN6Ods1Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Best friends Gethin Jones and Dr Xand Van Tulleken battle to hunt out the finest antique treasures. They cruise across the Welsh border in a couple of rather large classic American motors, guided by experts Irita Marriott and Serhat Ahmet. Xand and Serhat discover their shared love of ceramics and set out to find the perfect piece to take to auction, while Irita hopes Gethin’s command of the Welsh language will give them an advantage. And there are mind games in the battle of the porcelain pigs. Taking a break from shopping, Gethin and Irita take a train ride into the past to learn about Wales’s railway history. Meanwhile, our other pair head to Chester to discover the impact the Romans had on Britain’s pottery production, and amateur potter Xand tries his hand at throwing a pot just like an ancient Roman. Then it’s off to Derby to see who the high-flier at the final showdown will be.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122210000 +0000" stop="20221122214500 +0000" catchup-id="1ElES7S2uQ-jGxvVRVzMYd1Fw2n1IhnKIJzPLxzQ"><title>Louis Theroux Interviews... : Katherine Ryan</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Louis spends time with Canadian comedian, actor and writer Katherine Ryan. Since her arrival in the UK 15 years ago, Katherine has become one of the country's most outspoken performers, and her career has grown from appearances on British panel shows to writing and executive producing her own television stand-up specials and performing in venues across the globe. Louis is invited to Katherine’s home for a frank, no-holds-barred conversation about her life and her comedy, including raising her daughter Violet as a single mum. Louis also accompanies Katherine as she performs her latest stand-up tour, Missus, in Southend-on-Sea, as well as a surprise set at a London comedy club. Louis also spends a rare day off with Katherine, Violet and Katherine's husband Bobby.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122214500 +0000" stop="20221122221500 +0000" catchup-id="P35vfr1MqzWWkOdCrFWJvctimBNAPLqDpx7qJ3k1"><title>Frankie Boyle's New World Order</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/Yt8fAoVbMGXYLN5kURdE1w.jpg"></icon><desc>Frankie Boyle returns to help make sense of this disconcerting time, tackling the biggest issues troubling the planet and making a string of bold and often outrageous statements, which he then picks apart with Desiree Burch, Sophie Duker, Josie Long and Thanyia Moore.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122221500 +0000" stop="20221122223000 +0000" catchup-id="5dhLwrWzkZAtCytmc7YqEH_SyeFD7vMsxYyyTQmG"><title>Mandy : SpaceMandy</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122223000 +0000" stop="20221122231500 +0000" catchup-id="h1BCdMK_ueWJsfX7M0_crdx_wEdNzPvVYV5OU76R"><title>Newsnight</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bUQ-JbBOx1dTvpjQEinXPw.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Victoria Derbyshire.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221122231500 +0000" stop="20221123001500 +0000" catchup-id="Xk_3A2AFAatLQo6nR7EiEcqDfynpCsu7cGxxyw1N"><title>The Secret Genius of Modern Life : Food Delivery App</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Hannah Fry tucks into the tech behind food delivery apps like Deliveroo and Just Eat, which are now used by 24 million people in the UK. Hannah meets the R&amp;D team behind food delivery titan Deliveroo, finds out how pensioners ordering Greggs revolutionised food delivery, and discovers how pizza made us fall in love with the internet in the 1990s.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123001500 +0000" stop="20221123011500 +0000" catchup-id="r4p-chfJNaGnt_w2MikKkRO0uBmdSLD__Bfyfj95"><title>Signed: Autumnwatch</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/7dAJ_0aHHbx4b_-Ucah3tw.jpg"></icon><desc>A deep dive into the changing nature of autumn, looking at the winners and losers as environmental patterns shift. In Norfolk, Chris Packham and Michaela Strachan showcase the surprising things that viewers have been seeing this autumn from around the country. Iolo Williams and Gillian Burke wow in Wales with marine marvels and mammals, including live bats departing en masse from their roost sites at dusk.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123011500 +0000" stop="20221123020000 +0000" catchup-id="amyY95kLvT28qe7kUzyUr8EQk1XTPG_Q1VWrOGGV"><title>Signed: Stanley Tucci: Searching For Italy</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/B-tgVt8AdBGQOtDdTH5n4Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Stanley Tucci visits Umbria, nicknamed the green heart of Italy. While this small, predominantly rural region lives in the shadow of its more glamorous neighbor, Tuscany, Umbria has an ancient history that predates even the Romans. With the highest consumption of pork per capita in Italy, Umbria is a carnivore's dream. From wild boar hunts to incredible black truffle farms, Tucci explores the riches this land has to offer whilst also questioning whether old traditions and centuries of religious orthodoxy are preventing younger generations from breaking through.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123020000 +0000" stop="20221123024500 +0000" catchup-id="MDGzzhuTYccfqqNzL0tkuAEqqaha1rzXZ3R4bulf"><title>Signed: Best Bakes Ever</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Actress and cake expert Jane Asher brings together a selection of recipes from the nation's favourite television chefs. Each episode gives baking fans another chance to experience classic dishes from the likes of the James Martin, Mary Berry and Paul Hollywood, the Hairy Bikers, Raymond Blanc, Nigella Lawson, Tom Kerridge, Lorraine Pascale and Rachel Khoo. There is added insight and appreciation from Jane herself too. Whether it is cakes, pies, puddings or main courses - this greatest hits of baking is a must for anyone with a need to knead, and should help inspire even more of us to start getting creative in the kitchen.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123024500 +0000" stop="20221123063000 +0000" catchup-id="xZH_O2116rno59-AtyKPVvh1sLJzup_9MvxRFaUk"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123063000 +0000" stop="20221123071500 +0000" catchup-id="huL-Fb1GJv2hrbMbtrZzEoLOiS70ZBMESNxSQCwg"><title>Bargain Hunt</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/_n4I9rQNXfb1yt_rdabD_Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Eric Knowles and the teams shop for antiques in Guildford with experts Raj Bisram and Stephanie Connell. Eric also visits a former Victorian workhouse and samples the grub once served up to inmates.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123071500 +0000" stop="20221123080000 +0000" catchup-id="JUAcli3AQh4NAPpQqZYzI-sn67sB1HHFRRLtlptQ"><title>Money for Nothing</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/7QssTsRrKA7Ad2b5d9jQFw.jpg"></icon><desc>Jacqui Joseph is browsing the boots at Altrincham recycling centre in Greater Manchester, on the hunt for three items worthy of a second chance. She has her sights set on an old side table in need of a bold new look, upcyclers Katie Stone and Sophie Lawrence tackle a quartet of tired dining chairs, and blacksmiths Bex Simon and Dave Harris attempt to turn a pair of metal gates into money-makers.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123080000 +0000" stop="20221123090000 +0000" catchup-id="V489wQZ8auaSBgeaPHdHp90O-IgB0hYVfoN1Xsd5"><title>Signed: MasterChef: The Professionals</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/9iEXf-1bVLUoRAvPsDSWxA.jpg"></icon><desc>In the second quarter-final, the four best chefs from the week’s heats return to the kitchen. Tonight, they must prove themselves to Anna and Marcus in two challenges that would unnerve even the most experienced chefs. First, Anna and Marcus set the contenders an Invention Test with a twist. They must create a dish that showcases as many different textures as possible using a larder that includes seafood, fish, meat, fruit, vegetables, spices, nuts, pastas and pulses. Starting from scratch, who will best use the 70 minutes to deliver a plate full of contrasting textures that also tastes delicious? Next, the chefs must raise their game yet again when they cook for food writers Leyla Kazim, William Sitwell and Grace Dent. With a two-course menu of their own design, this is their chance to catch the eye of three people whose word can make or break careers. Only the most talented chefs will make it through to the semi-finals.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123090000 +0000" stop="20221123100000 +0000" catchup-id="RW_q9EF64VPppoukLiJTz_BforOmGDcTyDfFP5KS"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/O4C25N7vCNk5hoXbwDrnIw.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest headlines, breaking news and sport from the BBC newsroom.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123100000 +0000" stop="20221123111500 +0000" catchup-id="J88s2Iov6O4aZWa2qjHY9r27JN5oSwNZ-MoBk01O"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/O4C25N7vCNk5hoXbwDrnIw.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123111500 +0000" stop="20221123130000 +0000" catchup-id="vsAzbL4GwmS4_b06o4nuY0A0qDXccNSOVM2A66eo"><title>Politics Live</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The big political issues of the day.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123130000 +0000" stop="20221123134500 +0000" catchup-id="ga_YhXHJo6KhR6LyM7gDZeaGO3odjTAkZQAUju1o"><title>Best House in Town : Leicester: Wildcard</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/Pyk0kvy9AYicOqXjF8JDiw.jpg"></icon><desc>The owners of three wildcard properties hand over their keys to a team of discerning neighbours in the hope of being judged to have the best house in town. Competing are a 100-year-old Dutch barge, a modern mansion and a 'Scandinavian barn'-inspired rebuild.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123134500 +0000" stop="20221123141500 +0000" catchup-id="ZLue6fbOaQ4TMhXJQ097aeFWaECxVkgBbpUQ28yg"><title>Eggheads</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/kxjywN32Sf7ZLWFid1pwVQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Jeremy Vine hosts the show where every day a new team of challengers take on what is probably the greatest quiz team in Britain, made up of some of the country's top quizzers.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123141500 +0000" stop="20221123144500 +0000" catchup-id="4UHhxULR1cDtb0T9VCLGMyTer3W8rwk_F90cCqoS"><title>Lightning</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/O9yEJFaPlaRcdU7dXdvZEg.jpg"></icon><desc>Comedian Zoe Lyons presents the electrifyingly fast quiz with a £3,000 jackpot.Six plucky contestants compete across six rounds testing their general knowledge, quick thinking and speedy reactions whilst our ruthless spotlight patrols the studio.The contestants' motivation in each round is simple: stay out of the light and you'll be alright!</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123144500 +0000" stop="20221123151500 +0000" catchup-id="39zvK8v0VLIZ9CLxHpOL_7I1g3s-ylDslOXtiCwx"><title>Fish Town</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/A3KxsSlg81R09sW1uc7BbA.jpg"></icon><desc>Six-part series about the UK's biggest fishing port, Peterhead. The fishing boat Zenith sets out from Fraserburgh, 20 miles away from Peterhead, in search of whitefish and prawns.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123151500 +0000" stop="20221123161500 +0000" catchup-id="zKMfaDUJaaUv-vkgRSXaVxgJv-5Qbm8xGagw_C4Z"><title>The Great British Sewing Bee</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/o_79JWnD_9h6be-qOHn0IQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Joe Lycett hosts as the ten remaining home sewers return to the nation's most famous sewing room for gent's classics week. In a gentle first test of tailoring, judges Patrick Grant and Esme Young kick off the Pattern Challenge with a Sewing Bee first - a baker boy cap. The cap requires perfect symmetry in its construction, a supporting brim and a snug fit to get that full Peaky Blinders look. Next, in the Transformation Challenge, they have just 90 minutes to smarten up and convert secondhand men's jackets and blazers into a garment for a woman. Finally, for the Made to Measure challenge the sewers must make a casual utility jacket, which should have a relaxed fit and include at least three pockets. Who will make something for the perfect gent and win Garment of the Week, and who will become the third sewer to leave the Great British Sewing Bee?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123161500 +0000" stop="20221123171500 +0000" catchup-id="PkotUE0dWj9iqyritIlVz6EF5GVexFo8BWRdee8K"><title>Kate Humble: Into the Volcano</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>In this first episode of a two-part documentary, Kate Humble joins a team of geologists on a journey right to the heart of one of the most active volcanoes in the world. Located on the island of Tanna in the Vanuatu archipelago, Yasur erupts constantly, firing out red-hot lava bombs and showering the island in thick black ash. To discover whether another devastating eruption might happen, the team needs to collect a lava bomb the minute it is hurled from the crater. As they prepare for their death-defying mission, Kate explores the island and discovers how the volcano shapes the lives, traditions and beliefs of everyone who lives in its shadow.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123171500 +0000" stop="20221123180000 +0000" catchup-id="-yoXRhMJGcbKmaIVFJNoPENQ4_yJ95qh6Jdv6hak"><title>Flog It! : Huddersfield 30</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123180000 +0000" stop="20221123183000 +0000" catchup-id="I3sRuPDfAp_tMn1MwkuB8w1PIJcIfMxVe6vssUkb"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games : Week 12: Wednesday</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/QTvvZ81udNlpPp2OS-TMAQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Every day this week, former winners Maggie Aderin-Pocock, Cariad Lloyd, Gareth Malone and Mike Wozniak take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Facing their second chance to win a prize, will the winning stars opt for the House of Games golden goblets, or will they be tempted with the must-have House of Games golden fondue set?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123183000 +0000" stop="20221123190000 +0000" catchup-id="uVu9nt8OpD41SI5Xy5Wr99El9o8gVjOANTj7apnD"><title>Strictly It Takes Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/jBI3R8x1LdHWuBnckASH_A.jpg"></icon><desc>Janette Manrara dishes up more gossip and behind-the-scenes action from Strictly.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123190000 +0000" stop="20221123193000 +0000" catchup-id="EkHsXUFBdqjbn1cHaXVDPkDlyhlmg00wP9dQ5MT9"><title>The One Show</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/R8qfJ9w3gj4N7H0YuztRag.jpg"></icon><desc>Alex Jones and Ronan Keating with the stories that matter from across the country.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123193000 +0000" stop="20221123200000 +0000" catchup-id="gQTuMsLwgF-1OSzThX3LGNq6ci6IrrpTo4Nzj-SO"><title>EastEnders</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/AIA24J34rsuQZvF_cXzqeg.jpg"></icon><desc>Mick has the rug pulled out from under him. Lexi is determined to get to the bottom of what’s going on. Rocky makes a shocking implication but quickly backtracks.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123200000 +0000" stop="20221123210000 +0000" catchup-id="IUSbrf2TanJcC4G7VYJqMvmjwtaiSrKnBxJv3mzp"><title>Celebrity Antiques Road Trip</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/5_Dul6Lg_CFLFmGN6Ods1Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Loose Women’s Kelle Bryan and Charlene White travel across Essex for another antiques trip. The experts joining them on their shopping spree are auctioneer Catherine Southon and dealer Ochuko Ojiri. From behind the wheel of a classic car, the two teams each set out with £400 to find the most profitable antiques. On the way, Charlene and Catherine discover the mysterious story of an 18th-century folk magician, while Kelle and Ochuko explore the cultural impact that the Windrush Generation had on British music.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123210000 +0000" stop="20221123220000 +0000" catchup-id="Dpg48MLnAPJCJQrMx3VJ19zG1ImImtTfu7eS40CI"><title>The Ice Cream Wars</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The inside story of how Glasgow’s housing schemes and the ice cream vans which served them became central to a criminal war, with deadly consequences.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123220000 +0000" stop="20221123223000 +0000" catchup-id="Heb_5JuB9yqA2VceWfI2yJgVfUym0NOKdX4pwbqf"><title>Two Doors Down : Dinner for Seven</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>There's great excitement as Colin introduces the neighbours to his new partner Anne Marie. But the gang are quickly taken aback by her enthusiastic approach to the dinner party.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123223000 +0000" stop="20221123231500 +0000" catchup-id="nobBVlzJ6uyy0fbHm-gb9sKYg40OBhXuSmLL-2vP"><title>Newsnight</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bUQ-JbBOx1dTvpjQEinXPw.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Victoria Derbyshire.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123231500 +0000" stop="20221123234500 +0000" catchup-id="WVIP0rDYOaHJ3HoMwx6BR_qyxXU63fk1bJeruNUH"><title>Unspun World with John Simpson</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/CkI1Rc6kHuSpIQ4Wgt1MpA.jpg"></icon><desc>John Simpson, in discussion with the BBC's unparalleled range of experts across the world, examines whether there is growing fatigue in Europe with the war in Ukraine, analyses the significance of North Korea’s leader Kim Jong Un appearing with his daughter for the first time, and looks at what it means for the global population to reach 8 billion people.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221123234500 +0000" stop="20221124001500 +0000" catchup-id="Ihq2Zc9_bzv4O5aKPy2LvOvlFZDGK2EnV27HnkOq"><title>QI : 'T' Animals</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/mWzi8A0HiCWq5DjM2FsZkQ.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124001500 +0000" stop="20221124011500 +0000" catchup-id="-OsVcbxp_SF7O4G4O0Vsm8AbbgY8WFRZxW1lNFyB"><title>Signed: Autumnwatch</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/7dAJ_0aHHbx4b_-Ucah3tw.jpg"></icon><desc>Chris and Michaela showcase the insects who live at Wild Ken Hill, with the macro studio set up to showcase bugs and creepy crawlies in incredible detail. And will the beavers make an appearance live in the show? Iolo Williams and Gillian Burke showcase the sights and sounds of Wales. Do dolphins have Welsh accents? And Autumnwatch has once again teamed up with Children in Need, meeting nature-loving siblings Sophia and Leo, who are dealing with a disease that affects so many families, cancer.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124011500 +0000" stop="20221124021500 +0000" catchup-id="ltVLYoFHoOXCkrhOpjkB-_4ppo_h_iZEIU7lqgL9"><title>Signed: The Elon Musk Show</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>By 2016, Elon Musk is moving fast with several new business ideas: building underground tunnels, creating chips that can be inserted into people's brains and attempting to build the biggest battery factory the world has ever seen. All the while he is edging closer to his ultimate dream of taking humanity to Mars. As Elon’s businesses reach unprecedented levels of success, his celebrity grows, but his behaviour comes under ever greater scrutiny.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124021500 +0000" stop="20221124030000 +0000" catchup-id="vMyhVYsuasD6fLquaUEDDbM2KBmR6E6Lbx05SOTb"><title>Signed: Best Bakes Ever</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Actress and cake expert Jane Asher brings together a selection of recipes from the nation's favourite television chefs. Each episode gives baking fans another chance to experience classic dishes from the likes of the James Martin, Mary Berry and Paul Hollywood, the Hairy Bikers, Raymond Blanc, Nigella Lawson, Tom Kerridge, Lorraine Pascale and Rachel Khoo. There is added insight and appreciation from Jane herself too. Whether it is cakes, pies, puddings or main courses - this greatest hits of baking is a must for anyone with a need to knead, and should help inspire even more of us to start getting creative in the kitchen.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124030000 +0000" stop="20221124063000 +0000" catchup-id="kKeM2sucMB4OoJgPvgL92fqVEbEeiIQWtr0leTBI"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124063000 +0000" stop="20221124071500 +0000" catchup-id="qXu2vMqZrBJRTM45kQxO90EA5D4GSB1GptJEctO3"><title>Bargain Hunt : Football Special</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/_n4I9rQNXfb1yt_rdabD_Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Caroline Hawley presents a fever-pitched football special from Detling in Kent. Two teams of football fans shop for three items to take to auction, with the help of experts Tim Weeks and Nick Hall. There’s plenty of friendly rivalry as they try to score the best deals, but who will come out as champions? Caroline meets Baz Davison to discuss his collection of retro World Cup 1994 football shirts.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124071500 +0000" stop="20221124080000 +0000" catchup-id="JmPpW6TDuGLixBH1A-m0jq2ZFlQqbNaNREUjO7Q7"><title>Escape to the Country : Argyll and Bute</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/3oX-Fb_En1VQaDIMqBzT9w.jpg"></icon><desc>An adventurous young couple from Nottinghamshire are looking to move county and country to Argyll and Bute, where Sonali Shah has some splendid Scottish properties waiting to show them. In an action-packed few days, Sonali also takes to the water on a paddleboard and to the air in a seaplane, delighting at the spectacular views on offer from above.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124080000 +0000" stop="20221124083000 +0000" catchup-id="8XSV1z4EzcAvQ_rAJ0KYEWtAEAZzfdPoU2REFIG4"><title>Signed: Iolo: A Wild Life</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/lYc5LyuYb1FV6U9KvNU8RA.jpg"></icon><desc>Iolo Williams remembers finding lizards and slow worms on country lanes in Snowdonia back in 2000. He recalls watching a kestrel take a lizard while walking the Ceredigion coastal path between Cwmtydu and Llangrannog, and bottlenose dolphins hunting for fish off the Mwnt. Iolo also digs up his best scuba dives. Off the Pembrokeshire coast, he found an extraordinary congregation of giant spider crabs mating, a huge sea cucumber and fantastic coral fans. Twenty metres below off the Lleyn Peninsula, he found a thorny Mediterranean mantis shrimp burrowing on the sea bottom. Other gems from the archive include rock pool wildlife in Oxwich Bay, singing birds and the best view ever of a peregrine nest at South Stack, Anglesey.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124083000 +0000" stop="20221124090000 +0000" catchup-id="BWshEoHFsn7SLfuLKNanYhFVv3rAbRzXDpOiClqQ"><title>Signed: Between the Covers</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/8wf6Lq-RQXgwlOUeULrMyg.jpg"></icon><desc>Sara is joined by broadcaster and author Graham Norton, The One Show’s Alex Jones, actor Amanda Abbington and former marine turned presenter JJ Chalmers. They share their favourite books and review this week’s two book club choices: the new book pick, The Perfect Golden Circle, by Benjamin Myers, and the first in a selection from the Booker Prize backlist, Cloud Atlas, by David Mitchell.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124090000 +0000" stop="20221124100000 +0000" catchup-id="rtw3YKAaIGtCjnWgZvYvwBKxzpSK7rAn03KLqzBJ"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/O4C25N7vCNk5hoXbwDrnIw.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest headlines, breaking news and sport from the BBC newsroom.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124100000 +0000" stop="20221124120000 +0000" catchup-id="FYB7lKRlhnxsA6cEPc3QUs2PWZTrXE0xCXAHeezH"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/O4C25N7vCNk5hoXbwDrnIw.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124120000 +0000" stop="20221124124500 +0000" catchup-id="RsKFp89gLAHNyYpBjmH8ISBkGSADpVtflW33VCpU"><title>Bargain Hunt : Bath 19</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/_n4I9rQNXfb1yt_rdabD_Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Eric Knowles and today’s teams go bargain hunting at Bath Racecourse. In the running with the reds and blues are experts Stephanie Connell and Raj Bisram, and weighing up the odds at the auction is auctioneer Tim Weeks. Eric takes time out to look at surgical equipment from the past courtesy of the Bath Medical Museum.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124124500 +0000" stop="20221124133000 +0000" catchup-id="1qLfk3HS2IRAz4drj4nXvs-Li-wm4N_YE0YdQWz_"><title>Politics Live</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The big political issues of the day.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124133000 +0000" stop="20221124141500 +0000" catchup-id="4CZHJZRg2dJKzryWfdrz1qlZvbZzI9FcK4eI6MWN"><title>Best House in Town : Leicester: Semi-Detached</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/Pyk0kvy9AYicOqXjF8JDiw.jpg"></icon><desc>Three homeowners in Leicester compete for the title of best house in town. Battling it out for a place in the final are a fun, 'shabby chic' family home, a third-generation family home with some techy twists, and finally an Edwardian semi-detached house with some rather eclectic interiors.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124141500 +0000" stop="20221124144500 +0000" catchup-id="sCBkvSLzemNXtnieWghktENWNYm0r3hRgYJPdvzi"><title>Lightning</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/O9yEJFaPlaRcdU7dXdvZEg.jpg"></icon><desc>Comedian Zoe Lyons presents the electrifyingly fast quiz with a £3,000 jackpot.Six plucky contestants compete across six rounds testing their general knowledge, quick thinking and speedy reactions whilst our ruthless spotlight patrols the studio.The contestants' motivation in each round is simple: stay out of the light and you'll be alright!</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124144500 +0000" stop="20221124151500 +0000" catchup-id="wbDp61Lfn0e2m-_QC_ttXIOuFfGDiK1ii_j1WJeG"><title>Lightning</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/O9yEJFaPlaRcdU7dXdvZEg.jpg"></icon><desc>Comedian Zoe Lyons presents the electrifyingly fast quiz with a £3,000 jackpot.Six plucky contestants compete across six rounds testing their general knowledge, quick thinking and speedy reactions whilst our ruthless spotlight patrols the studio.The contestants' motivation in each round is simple: stay out of the light and you'll be alright!</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124151500 +0000" stop="20221124161500 +0000" catchup-id="agjUQXBUImS81LTKTsKN9046rNC7rKUWarDaAH3C"><title>The Great British Sewing Bee</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/X-6siZ3TvBexs7CZAhJzwA.jpg"></icon><desc>Joe Lycett hosts as the nine remaining sewers go global, taking on garments and techniques from around the world. First, they must follow a pattern as judges Patrick Grant and Esme Young ask them to make a French Breton top. Horizontal stripes must be perfectly matched, the wide-set boat neck must lie completely flat, and the fiddly button placket must be expertly constructed. Next up, it's the Transformation Challenge, with the sewers taking on sarongs. These colourful cloths must be transformed into a brand new outfit in just 90 minutes, making imaginative use of the distinctive, bold print. For their final challenge, the Made to Measure, the sewers make outfits inspired by the life and art of iconic Mexican artist Frida Kahlo. Known as much for her personal style as her vivid artwork, the sewers must use Kahlo as their inspiration while creating a modern garment that fits their model perfectly. Who will ace this creative brief and win Garment of the Week, and who will have to leave</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124161500 +0000" stop="20221124171500 +0000" catchup-id="fg-VZZdp3Gd5HpN5a8b-wOJk2ZC72SCm9TFqHRin"><title>Kate Humble: Into the Volcano</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Kate Humble joins a team of geologists on an awe-inspiring adventure to Ambrym in the Vanuatu island chain. Here, she undertakes an arduous journey to Marum - a volcano containing one of only five lava lakes on the planet - abseiling right to its heart to discover if another major eruption might be imminent. Along the way, she discovers how the volcano has shaped the customs and traditions of the islanders and discovers what it really means to live each day on the slopes of an erupting volcano.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124171500 +0000" stop="20221124180000 +0000" catchup-id="qohBKUHVms_9JeZOmNV1h927TS2MIYEL5lDBrc0w"><title>Flog It! : Rochester Cathedral</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124180000 +0000" stop="20221124183000 +0000" catchup-id="hkagW_Te_nASK1uS_PuwbMilE5EBcSMmstC91eK5"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games : Week 12: Thursday</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/QTvvZ81udNlpPp2OS-TMAQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Every day this week, former winners Maggie Aderin-Pocock, Cariad Lloyd, Gareth Malone and Mike Wozniak take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Facing their second chance to win a prize, will the winning stars opt for the House of Games golden goblets, or will they be tempted with the must-have House of Games golden fondue set?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124183000 +0000" stop="20221124190000 +0000" catchup-id="d9iaV_duj-8N4lGmUkBCnoFMJOg1CMXVl6pjLB7F"><title>Strictly It Takes Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/jBI3R8x1LdHWuBnckASH_A.jpg"></icon><desc>Janette Manrara dishes up more gossip and behind-the-scenes action from Strictly.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124190000 +0000" stop="20221124193000 +0000" catchup-id="842EEheI3-UfjWcBRJFuhb7j3ICRnmnZMMkwHMVu"><title>The One Show</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/R8qfJ9w3gj4N7H0YuztRag.jpg"></icon><desc>Alex Jones and Ronan Keating with the stories that matter from across the country.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124193000 +0000" stop="20221124200000 +0000" catchup-id="7-cJzAyRQDWQMY4qlvPoFy4aYlrwQh4prN6SKhKy"><title>EastEnders</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/AIA24J34rsuQZvF_cXzqeg.jpg"></icon><desc>Rocky is suspicious about Harvey’s new love interest. Eve is on a mission, but is she playing with fire?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124200000 +0000" stop="20221124210000 +0000" catchup-id="JhaHd63V3c94G-pOYY_7OYWG13BFZfdDPHdzI3mj"><title>The Secret Genius of Modern Life : Virtual Assistant</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Hannah Fry delves into the inner workings of virtual assistants like Amazon's Alexa, Google Assistant and Siri, which are now found in almost half of all UK homes. Hannah goes behind the scenes with Alexa's chief scientist, reveals how secret technology invented to hunt U-boats led to their targeted hearing, and discovers modern wireless networks' debt to a 1940s Hollywood star.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124210000 +0000" stop="20221124215500 +0000" catchup-id="EG0tSqkL1UGXAvkq1DwRW10n8GOoRsN6Nh1t4DEP"><title>The English : Vultures on the Line</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124215500 +0000" stop="20221124223000 +0000" catchup-id="LstkEPlPdbtXljIRaHmyHttMHv9pwuCN2RHkADPH"><title>Live at the Apollo</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/R2ZYBlQacXTt2yaq81nYYw.jpg"></icon><desc>Gina Yashere introduces surreal comedian Sam Simmons and rising star Ellie Taylor.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124223000 +0000" stop="20221124231500 +0000" catchup-id="8F115QinvR9tYnTNpwf4s-x2NxIdmFOcVfnmmVn9"><title>Newsnight</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bUQ-JbBOx1dTvpjQEinXPw.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Mark Urban.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221124231500 +0000" stop="20221125012000 +0000" catchup-id="zxxehqF8P8Ynp3hycrB0_ZWoSNBD3IA5ttweUgv3"><title>Ready Player One</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/NGW7ojeTKbl59ZM7tdlp5Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Gamer fantasy. When the creator of a virtual reality gaming world dies, he bequeathes his fortune as an 'Easter Egg' to one lucky gamer - but to win it, players must enter the virtual world for a dangerous and action-packed treasure hunt</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125012000 +0000" stop="20221125022000 +0000" catchup-id="BM-nYG0jFTfdnzMrd2rPnoGu0VWXG023c_7t7eNq"><title>Signed: Autumnwatch</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/7dAJ_0aHHbx4b_-Ucah3tw.jpg"></icon><desc>Chris and Michaela bring the final instalment of the wildlife dramas that have been unfolding all week at Wild Ken Hill. Gillian and Iolo will be catching up on the latest action from one of the biggest bat roosts in Wales. There's a look at how the falling leaves of autumn lead to extraordinary wildlife dramas in our rivers, plus the woman releasing injured bats after they've successfully completed flight tests in her bat-friendly garage.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125022000 +0000" stop="20221125035000 +0000" catchup-id="DGZcOK-0iGOg4g6ZG0Ss2aUOGgqEcmWqHDSCtQwU"><title>Signed: Strictly Come Dancing: Blackpool Special : Week 9: Blackpool Special</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/vseWTytrbafNTnrVWRtn4Q.jpg"></icon><desc>After a two-year absence, Strictly Come Dancing returns to the iconic Blackpool Tower Ballroom. The show opens with an incredible routine celebrating all things Blackpool from our judges and professional dancers before our remaining couples take to the most famous sprung floor in the country. Who will steal the limelight?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125035000 +0000" stop="20221125043000 +0000" catchup-id="kgAHKCgqng9AyZnAorwsF57xIxLjhSL2aiqaLdcU"><title>Signed: Strictly Come Dancing: The Results : Week 9 Results</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>It’s back to the Tower for the results show. Our professional dancers show us what Blackpool has meant to them in their poignant opening routine, and the brilliant Sam Ryder performs in the ballroom. At this stage of the competition, no-one wants to go home. Who will the judges save for another week?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125043000 +0000" stop="20221125063000 +0000" catchup-id="yl5vRVAuj8paRQDr426IkVR-XV6On03qwZSwciWh"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125063000 +0000" stop="20221125071500 +0000" catchup-id="2jeeJIA9U6T8YIZ1vtZH6flDBx4oQE1VBWJCniwJ"><title>Bargain Hunt : Ardingly 27</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/_n4I9rQNXfb1yt_rdabD_Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Charlie Ross and the teams visit Ardingly Antiques Fair with experts Caroline Hawley and Tim Weeks. Charlie heads to nearby Amberley Museum to learn about the history of firefighting in Britain.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125071500 +0000" stop="20221125081500 +0000" catchup-id="eqAJhr9VHGjLc4A2WNK3dUmKpgdAugUF2bRbrBnA"><title>Homes Under the Hammer</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/Honvrz_XaSQZKyAyWRd86w.jpg"></icon><desc>In Maltby, near Rotherham, clever budgeting helps a woman transform a house in a poor state into her forever home, while developers, also with tight budgets, work wonders on their auction buys in Dunscroft, near Doncaster, and Havercroft, near Wakefield.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125081500 +0000" stop="20221125091500 +0000" catchup-id="51pwcqGDmNHB-4HCnPccgwgqHaNd06JWglOS0Ujj"><title>Signed: Trawlermen: Hunting the Catch : The Million Pound Catch</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Scalloper Golden Promise is pushing force-6 winds to get to newly opening scallops beds ahead of his rivals. With the boat first to the grounds, they are in for a big pay day – but only once they cover the £8,000 fuel expenses to get here. Family-owned trawler Adenia leaves Lerwick aiming to land 1,000 tonnes of mackerel in Norway in just three days' time. Shetland skipper George Anderson has 11 crew, eight of whom are family, and he is hoping the fish will meet the grade to sell into the lucrative Asian sushi market. If it does, George and the crew could be in for a million-pound pay day. Skipper Ivan Toms and 25-year-old son Rhys fish Maxine’s Pride, one of the smallest and oldest trawlers in the UK fleet. In recent years, fishing has been a struggle, with little money to reinvest in the 35-year-old boat. Fishing Cornwall’s inshore waters - reserved for smaller fishing boats - can they catch enough to give themselves a wage and put money aside for repairs?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125091500 +0000" stop="20221125100000 +0000" catchup-id="JLTSegmb8h9DiXp1_9grbvBq4vEMOwj2JgLAGD8-"><title>Animal Park</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/YXoOyVfs7UX2U260lXHZYg.jpg"></icon><desc>There is more news about Dave the Wolf, who has been suffering from a mysterious illness, and the keepers have a tough decision to make.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125100000 +0000" stop="20221125103000 +0000" catchup-id="76CQ5W9PkNkybVAugXbJ3r4cPhcm0D0xat6qi5bL"><title>The Farmers' Country Showdown : Moseley Veg</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Sheep and arable farmers John and his son Ed head to the vibrant Moseley Farmers’ Market, but when they arrive, their unusual pitch threatens to put a dent in their earnings. Meanwhie, the stoic Styan family need to sell as many vegetables as possible to make some much-needed repairs to their windblown farm.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125103000 +0000" stop="20221125111500 +0000" catchup-id="xdxklQgBGIkHXmDoVYzJBHRub7cePRzei8AxVkE-"><title>Dom Does America : Coastguard</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/4LuIWxGVf7wGB3uiogWShA.jpg"></icon><desc>Dom’s patrolling the seas and skies, working as a coastguard in Corpus Christi, Texas. After tortuous survival training, Dom is cleared for take-off and joins an airborne security patrol under helicopter pilot Lieutenant Harry Lehman. For the second half of his shift, Dom ditches the aviator suit and joins petty officer Trey Hicks at Port Aransas boat station. On constant standby to give lifesaving assistance, they drill emergency evacuations with a hovering chopper, before patrolling the water into the night on the lookout for illegal fishing and smuggling of people or drugs. How will Dom handle a day in the life of America’s 5th military service?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125111500 +0000" stop="20221125121500 +0000" catchup-id="uxXatyf780HwYVAgwcKll0qHw8_AZdz1gtrrv45-"><title>Homes Under the Hammer</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/Honvrz_XaSQZKyAyWRd86w.jpg"></icon><desc>Dion's seeing double in Cheshire, as he looks around a pair of houses which share a single back garden. Martel gets the chills in Tyne and Wear when she visits a two-bed auction property with hardly any windows left intact. And Martin is spooked by the 'wall of doom' behind a three-bed end-of-terrace in the Rhondda Valley.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125121500 +0000" stop="20221125124500 +0000" catchup-id="LhG5W1TJJJl7LPdhXMcnIwlhrVJ1XWdwC9UMXSkU"><title>Bargain Hunt : Kingston</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/_n4I9rQNXfb1yt_rdabD_Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Anita Manning oversees today's Bargain Hunt, which comes from Kingston-upon-Thames. Catherine Southon and Danny Sebastian are the experts helping today's teams spend £300 on three items that might make a profit at auction in Chiswick.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125124500 +0000" stop="20221125133000 +0000" catchup-id="WY5zcGSEUG7-4cjqlmkkhzB6FVhejZvCFUdcYv1S"><title>Politics Live</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of the week’s proceedings at Westminster and the regional governments.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125133000 +0000" stop="20221125141500 +0000" catchup-id="J_wjYAB3ZRmKNcNcRMsZjGBrglerBb-aKRS7crNz"><title>Best House in Town : Leicester: Final</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/Pyk0kvy9AYicOqXjF8JDiw.jpg"></icon><desc>Today the judges revisit all of this week’s finalists to decide who deserves the ultimate accolade of the Best House in Town.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125141500 +0000" stop="20221125154000 +0000" catchup-id="eH17f-y2cRY98GylKCeJ1hV6uIGNyeBBv18Y6yte"><title>Christmas in Toyland</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/E2WUIa0KtwRXGbZJ2fdhEg.jpg"></icon><desc>Data analyst Charlie is sent by her boss at the Big Teddy Toyland company to examine first-hand why one of their stores is kicking the downward sales trend. At store 24 in New Jersey, she meets manager Grant, who has a contempt for corporate life and tries to retain the spirit of his grandfather, who also ran a toy store.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125154000 +0000" stop="20221125170000 +0000" catchup-id="npuq1xq7RxdlL1K3_C3CydpzV-kW0a7Was3CdgDZ"><title>Baking All the Way</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Accomplished restaurateur and cookery book author Julie Wilson, from Chicago, is about to publish her new Christmas-themed curated recipe book when she finds herself in Wisconsin, attempting to wrangle a gingerbread recipe from widower Kris Thompson, the owner of bakery store The Homestead.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125170000 +0000" stop="20221125171500 +0000" catchup-id="kukUObV2lmHm9lkNYJ53UTuHW6TqOGtlfwZpk93I"><title>Beechgrove Repotted</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Kirsty creates four practical, pretty and eco-friendly garden items from recycled materials. From a living picture frame filled with succulents constructed from leftover wood at Beechgrove, to a fairy garden made out of broken terracotta pots and a terrarium out of a second-hand glass teapot.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125171500 +0000" stop="20221125180000 +0000" catchup-id="joLX6oJya9uoZHNu-i2s4_8YjnCPOTrDrAGiKDkc"><title>Flog It! : Series 16 Revisited</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125180000 +0000" stop="20221125183000 +0000" catchup-id="jbo5VWTPfzrLj2ZsYkFps9Sh1dBJrl11zYjU_4sw"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games : Week 12: Friday</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/QTvvZ81udNlpPp2OS-TMAQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Every day this week, former winners Maggie Aderin-Pocock, Cariad Lloyd, Gareth Malone and Mike Wozniak take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Facing their second chance to win a prize, will the winning stars opt for the House of Games golden goblets, or will they be tempted with the must-have House of Games golden fondue set?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125183000 +0000" stop="20221125190000 +0000" catchup-id="LvHWpmG2xaO09Ep1tuhNs84ZkPgBWWEwAAmE2DCJ"><title>Strictly It Takes Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/jBI3R8x1LdHWuBnckASH_A.jpg"></icon><desc>Rylan is on hand with more Strictly exclusives and is joined by a trio of celebrity super fans. Plus a sneak peak at the remaining couples’ rehearsals in the Strictly studio.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125190000 +0000" stop="20221125200000 +0000" catchup-id="WrfJPXoN4puE-iFrjRLeokTstfTFI8aKuykTZeot"><title>Your Garden Made Perfect : Tracey And Jake</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/s8TsM_S5eDCgogRRB_2yaw.jpg"></icon><desc>Tracey and Jake have a decent-sized, south-facing garden in West Sussex, but the space simply doesn’t work for their family. As a full-time wheelchair user, Tracey struggles to navigate the tricky slopes and awkward drops of the garden, and gets frustrated that she can only venture into certain parts without assistance. Jake, meanwhile, finds the space uninspiring and gets tired of trying to keep it all looking neat and tidy. He dreams of a low-maintenance solution. Their daughter Poppy would love the garden to be somewhere she can escape into and enjoy alone or with her parents.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125200000 +0000" stop="20221125210000 +0000" catchup-id="MdGmAXYF0q4NIirgvYTmOKNk90rzfK5Eq1W5B82V"><title>Celebrity Antiques Road Trip</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/5_Dul6Lg_CFLFmGN6Ods1Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Breaking news - today’s star-studded shopping spree features award-winning journalist and newscaster Nina Hossain, along with fellow reporter Lucrezia Millarini. This pair of newsies are driving a custard-coloured 1955 Ford Pop Hot Rod, with expert advice provided by Dorset’s Tim Medhurst and Geordie-boy Steven Moore, who are piloting a 1960s Ford Thames between the antique shops and emporia. Their shopping bonanza between Nottinghamshire and Derbyshire will end with an ‘and finally’ at an auction in Buckinghamshire. Along the way Nina and Steven will learn about the unique Derbyshire tradition of well dressing, while Lucrezia and Tim find out about an invention which heralded the industrial revolution. Nina finds a love letter from the past and a silver brooch, while Lucrezia finds a jewellery casket that features a monkey riding an elephant – an item that’s sure to make big news at auction.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125210000 +0000" stop="20221125220000 +0000" catchup-id="nWukREf_uxEQMY-t6wlb1TnAjJGD1gz6h3U6OMTt"><title>Agatha Christie: Lucy Worsley on the Mystery Queen : Cat Among the Pigeons</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Lucy Worsley explores Agatha Christie’s haunted, unconventional early life to discover the origins of her talent for murder – and uncovers some carefully concealed secrets.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125220000 +0000" stop="20221125223000 +0000" catchup-id="FWMgyNzE05YnFSsKApElaflXoLIr0RTejboa0LkK"><title>QI : Television</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/mWzi8A0HiCWq5DjM2FsZkQ.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125223000 +0000" stop="20221125230500 +0000" catchup-id="-laO-GZK9UxWQhJhRT8oW_3-sCaaD311kjz0_0m_"><title>Newsnight</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bUQ-JbBOx1dTvpjQEinXPw.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Faisal Islam.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125230500 +0000" stop="20221125233500 +0000" catchup-id="OATvrYY0YIuyWGxWPIE9Nzs1dFs8tsGxW_ZLGqMj"><title>Frankie Boyle's New World Order</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/Yt8fAoVbMGXYLN5kURdE1w.jpg"></icon><desc>Frankie Boyle returns to help make sense of this disconcerting time, tackling the biggest issues troubling the planet and making a string of bold and often outrageous statements, which he then picks apart with Desiree Burch, Sophie Duker, Josie Long and Thanyia Moore.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221125233500 +0000" stop="20221126003500 +0000" catchup-id="gl-_pxPm9iphlwfeqhsPD4xnKcHen9ViIV_9snyN"><title>Hong Kong's Fight for Freedom</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>In October 2019, as Beijing celebrates 70 years of the People’s Republic of China, Hong Kong is being torn apart by violent protests. Using groundbreaking artificial intelligence to protect the identities of the protesters, this film tells the story of four young people locked in a brutal battle with the authorities to defend their way of life. As the police response turns deadly, the protesters respond with violence of their own. Families turn against each other, and the city is brought to its knees, but the protesters feel they are fighting for their freedom and refuse to give in. Holed up in a university campus, surrounded by police and with little response from the government, the protesters make their final stand. Meanwhile, Beijing is preparing a crackdown that will change the face of Hong Kong forever.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126003500 +0000" stop="20221126010500 +0000" catchup-id="k5r-gByqioA93B965V0l3y0by4hHI6JoKmH-vxFe"><title>Signed: Panorama : Cost of Living: Can't Afford My Home</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/5pVNsTdyebLeGLpayWONiw.jpg"></icon><desc>What does the winter hold for people struggling to get a home, or hold on to the one they already have? The rapid increase in interest rates has left many at breaking point. With mortgage rates up and rents soaring, Panorama spends time with those trying to survive. From young workers who’ve given up on ever owning a home of their own, to families facing eviction before Christmas. Reporter Richard Bilton investigates what’s gone wrong with the UK’s housing market.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126010500 +0000" stop="20221126020500 +0000" catchup-id="s_FA7Y1CVIY6Wo7VD45M8J16UA7XQ7qnQhY3e3GU"><title>Signed: The Hacienda - The Club That Shook Britain</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The story of Manchester's iconic Hacienda nightclub and music venue, 40 years after it opened, mixing insightful testimony from Peter Hook and Stephen Morris (members of New Order, the legendary band that funded it) with stories from famous regulars like Noel Gallagher and Shaun Ryder. The film hears from those who ran it in its heyday and ordinary people whose lives were changed forever by the Hacienda. Newly discovered archive footage reveals the radical origins of the club, as well as the music and madcap stories behind it. Iconic and infamous performances build up to the story of acid house, the youth movement that transformed a generation and changed Britain forever. This is the incredible but true story of a revolution that rose up from within the walls of a former warehouse in central Manchester.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126020500 +0000" stop="20221126025000 +0000" catchup-id="ydaWWFOEsfoZJHw8ab6rFfpE3mPPyH9tn6fXy3K0"><title>Signed: Louis Theroux Interviews... : Yungblud</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Louis meets Dominic Harrison, aka singer and musician Yungblud, often regarded as one of the UK music scene's brightest stars. Louis joins Yungblud in the USA, on the last two nights of a whirlwind tour. Along the way, Louis meets fans who follow their hero with almost religious intensity, attracted to his brand of emotionally charged music. In a Paris hotel during the European leg of the tour, Louis and Yungblud sit down to discuss a range of topics, including the artist's mental health, his sexuality and his response to outspoken critics. Louis also travels to Doncaster to spend time with Yungblud and his family, where they discuss his turbulent upbringing.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126025000 +0000" stop="20221126064000 +0000" catchup-id="XX4UCaES0tzV71kxl2HYj9ItwMXkTvpsLx8OJjM7"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126064000 +0000" stop="20221126064500 +0000" catchup-id="TB8l0DEj2h5ft3515rbnN7Xei94x_QqbiX_i5AQX"><title>Love Monster : Babysitting Day</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/eKm0H4f3WgNb6qPfZoWS6w.jpg"></icon><desc>It is Babysitting Day, and Love Monster is practising with Monster Teddy because he is going to look after a real baby. Just then, there is a knock at the door and it’s Caring-And-Sharing Koala with his baby, Quiet Koala. Caring-And-Sharing Koala places the sleeping baby in a basket and thanks Love Monster for looking after his pride and joy, before handing him a huge bag of things to keep the baby happy.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126064500 +0000" stop="20221126070000 +0000" catchup-id="P1hzXSPxYY_cSE_lVefTJ-obRaQJiNLpsMOZS3gq"><title>Go Jetters : Go Jet Academy: Rainbow</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/SrF6Oaf0TYcd3bBhYKWMPQ.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126070000 +0000" stop="20221126071000 +0000" catchup-id="MDYtBitQhoMqPB5v3qUPwQecAC2gdBCb4HQ0uuAm"><title>Go Jetters : Go Jet Academy: Lightning Bolt Blackout</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/SrF6Oaf0TYcd3bBhYKWMPQ.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126071000 +0000" stop="20221126072000 +0000" catchup-id="i1bvHQjfUmsvkulwLC8pXSB757vnNSKL4cGqqwZR"><title>Hey Duggee : The Get Indoors Badge</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/urGJSvyin8F9qZGeOiApxA.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126072000 +0000" stop="20221126073000 +0000" catchup-id="-LJ6Ec17PmktCQPULWTvklCznacTwpHbra-GJcbM"><title>Hey Duggee : The Day Off Badge</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/jcLr2-r6wquTwY1xGvrSIA.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126073000 +0000" stop="20221126073500 +0000" catchup-id="w8tdjqSlhMMzdK0Eh8y2rBu8uh804GpDbYch9w_G"><title>Shaun the Sheep : Go Bitzer Go!</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/Qa0fwBdW2CXPs4e4G5Z7VA.jpg"></icon><desc>Shaun tries to ensure that Bitzer won't be defeated in the box cart Grand Prix again.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126073500 +0000" stop="20221126075000 +0000" catchup-id="mDUlzMLuW6HSOE5adQg0FmqGtq-RJUu-KDTgSl23"><title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher: Unleashed! : The Comedy Crown</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/uJ55oL8XKAZEwSQSfpF-MQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Pieface enters a comedy contest, which makes him realize how funny he can be, and that motivates him to try to win the crown despite WilburCorp's meddling.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126075000 +0000" stop="20221126080000 +0000" catchup-id="q2JVcus9P97G7m7AZV8FqsFhKjoqFOwqA2ktjrCs"><title>Ninja Express : A Flag</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/D3dIgH9M7bGrvIcd7rG0lA.jpg"></icon><desc>The Ninjas battle a hungry space blob as they try to fulfill an order for a flag for astronaut Lewis Weaklegs to plant on the moon.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126080000 +0000" stop="20221126082500 +0000" catchup-id="MPdBVSAIY-XSNCVwvNlg8uUlkRdShA2_5fbscXvS"><title>The Deep : The Inside Story</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/DpXsAPT9eH2cIcw_DiSdkg.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126082500 +0000" stop="20221126083500 +0000" catchup-id="P_6aspxtTkt8EsIMNMgiLlIKjmVzJC_JDLejdG1I"><title>Odd Squad : Odd Squad in the Shadows, Part 1</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/LqVOlkr4n0WEoFGAN0E6rQ.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126083500 +0000" stop="20221126090000 +0000" catchup-id="JUkDTQSTxg_UB5RSg5DKqQM9D0nTkHCRzXPHtym1"><title>One Zoo Three : Tiger Time</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The brothers celebrate Chinese New Year with the big cats. Can some tasty Chinese lanterns help Luka the Amur leopard break the ice with his with neighbour Xizi?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126090000 +0000" stop="20221126090500 +0000" catchup-id="if59jV9yurFuz6jdbb07YMNgL74YfwbBIImNK9k1"><title>Newsround</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/HsG2NEk_PJ2ML7EYnugwRw.jpg"></icon><desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126090500 +0000" stop="20221126093000 +0000" catchup-id="3fnYKffWXwC5UX5Zd8EgDuggru-kOvHP_xHunW0b"><title>Nova Jones : Nil Points Nova</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Nova wants to win the Boodlebeegan Song Contest, but when she accidentally finds a way to enter, she discovers that not every competition needs to be won.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126093000 +0000" stop="20221126100000 +0000" catchup-id="h_HFh7jsJuhfnsY1VXwxmgQx86CozyvMU0fi2-cz"><title>Blue Peter : World Cup Football Party!</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/Ylvd0hPRjbJfR-1aicRhFA.jpg"></icon><desc>The team have got their boots on and are ready for kick-off as they celebrate the start of the 2022 World Cup! Richie is put through his paces by England's Phil Foden and Connor Gallagher AND goes head-to-head with Joel in a World Cup Party showdown!</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126100000 +0000" stop="20221126113000 +0000" catchup-id="nkXiz6vsRt3ibuA-djLfvPFiIPF43EBj1oGRkby7"><title>Saturday Kitchen</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/xp1C47rCE3FLQ8WxiL1ihQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Matt Tebbutt and chefs Owen Morgan and Sabrina Ghayour are joined by special guest Nick Grimshaw. There are great moments from the BBC food archive, including clips from Rick Stein, Marcus Wareing, Nigella Lawson and Keith Floyd, and drinks expert Helen McGinn is picking the wines to go with the studio dishes.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126113000 +0000" stop="20221126123000 +0000" catchup-id="kGl98mdLbhvBF3W82DCVFR19jCN0cP5doYBXL-7v"><title>Top of the Shop with Tom Kerridge : Sauces</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Four food producers with fledgling businesses test out their products. This time it is makers of cooking sauces competing against each other for one place in the final.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126123000 +0000" stop="20221126133000 +0000" catchup-id="0UW0oYKeeVxbeqZpAuJp8_ObXhJcIgPcKyEO8G71"><title>Britain's Secret Seas : The Power of the East</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Documentary series revealing Britain's stunning marine life, mysterious wrecks and issues that affect our seas. In this episode, the team set out to explore the waters off Britain's eastern coastline, an area where conditions are changing rapidly. Visiting the Farne Islands, they encounter England's largest colony of grey seals and set out to find out why these seals are coping better than their close cousins, the harbour seal. Elsewhere, Frank Pope looks at the wind turbine farms that are joining the gas and oil reserves of the North Sea in providing energy for the mainland, and Tooni Mahto looks at their effect on marine life. Paul Rose reveals the intriguing history of light vessels and the Thames Estuary, and also meets the 'Robofish' - a plastic imposter created to help shed light on how schools of fish move in synchronisation</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126133000 +0000" stop="20221126140000 +0000" catchup-id="Zk6-fQ5V5tI9EFPot3CNuc6PFvBDPZ5q5oGB41Mq"><title>Talking Pictures : Omar Sharif</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>A look back at the life of the actor Omar Sharif, who died in July 2015 at the age of 83. Using archive from his interviews with the BBC and featuring contributions from director David Lean, this episode explores Sharif's dramatic entrance into the film world of the 1960s with Lawrence of Arabia and Doctor Zhivago, sees him considering his reputation as a playboy, and examines how his passion for cards and gambling at one point threatened to eclipse his reputation as an actor.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126140000 +0000" stop="20221126171000 +0000" catchup-id="8tABwqWn9GYvPTyw6rma7fCWMzo7Qs3XYvc2p8iw"><title>Doctor Zhivago</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/GdhPAQnbtW6jHtKK21aeJA.jpg"></icon><desc>Epic adaptation of Boris Pasternak's Nobel Prize-winning novel about the tribulations of a Russian doctor and poet over three decades in the early part of the 20th century. Made an enemy of the state by the revolution because of his writing, Yuri Zhivago seeks solace in the woman brought into his life by the First World War</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126171000 +0000" stop="20221126182500 +0000" catchup-id="h9i_jQ8K9LeeMLIp1EqFqZKMhJTipgyPfgx84mLk"><title>Triathlon World Series Final Highlights</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/Zs-z2Arz3o3VkAOjXoSo3w.jpg"></icon><desc>The best of the breathless action from Abu Dhabi, with British stars including Alex Yee and Georgia Taylor-Brown among those seeking to be crowned world champions for 2022. Taylor-Brown, who won the world title in 2020, has won three races going into this seventh and final leg of the series to put herself in contention alongside fellow Brits Beth Potter and Sophie Coldwell. Standing in their way is Bermuda’s formidable Flora Duffy, the reigning Olympic, world and Commonwealth champion. In the elite men’s event, Yee faces a familiar adversary in New Zealand’s Hayden Wilde, who finished one place on the podium below the Brit at the 2020 Olympics and 2021 Commonwealth Games. Both men are looking for their first world title.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126182500 +0000" stop="20221126192500 +0000" catchup-id="ymlMjr6hp1lG_v7RgeoW0sDqFpocLfY2Utw_PBW0"><title>The Secret Genius of Modern Life : Virtual Assistant</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Hannah Fry delves into the inner workings of virtual assistants like Amazon's Alexa, Google Assistant and Siri, which are now found in almost half of all UK homes. Hannah goes behind the scenes with Alexa's chief scientist, reveals how secret technology invented to hunt U-boats led to their targeted hearing, and discovers modern wireless networks' debt to a 1940s Hollywood star.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126192500 +0000" stop="20221126202500 +0000" catchup-id="-S4isbvLTQGcrAm-LRh7_TibXpcFq92YOkKVXdso"><title>Horizon : Super Telescope: Mission to the Edge of the Universe</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/Vc3fbExLy7xlLDPw05-WJg.jpg"></icon><desc>The inside story of the James Webb Space Telescope, following the Nasa team building the £8 billion device and the scientists taking its first image of distant stars and galaxies.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126202500 +0000" stop="20221126210000 +0000" catchup-id="1KvPIoqG2gx2kqZrI_5O1_I6F4wMUWZRC-zRAQtD"><title>Dad's Army : Boots, Boots, Boots</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/z0QYrPofPxn3UK2ZIsrzgg.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126210000 +0000" stop="20221126223000 +0000" catchup-id="nHMoe4xkWo-EuyvNvoao2fOvD_fV8qeQ8hwFSxS6"><title>Jimi Hendrix Experience: Music, Money, Madness in Maui</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Chronicling Jimi Hendrix's visit to Maui in July 1970, this documentary tells the story of Rainbow Bridge, an ill-fated independent film produced by Hendrix's manager, Michael Jeffery. Jeffery secured a $300,000 advance against the promise of a soundtrack album by Hendrix - the first time a movie was funded solely by an album. But without a script or professional actors, the shoot proved to be one of excess. With The Jimi Hendrix Experience already booked to play Honolulu, director Chuck Wein planned to film them playing on the slope of the dormant Haleakala volcano. Whilst the show was a stunning success, the same could not be said for Rainbow Bridge. Featuring previously unseen colour footage of the performance as well as interviews with key players, including The Jimi Hendrix Experience bassist Billy Cox and drummer Mitch Mitchell, Rainbow Bridge director Chuck Wein and actor Michael Hynson, and friends of Jimi such as Collette Faron.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126223000 +0000" stop="20221126234500 +0000" catchup-id="rJbavNO5G5kasmmbX9xlW7EpnomUdBAGBNf4YqT1"><title>Jimi Hendrix: Voodoo Child</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/Oo05XsGGuCbIgmw8VdwVJQ.jpg"></icon><desc>40 years after Jimi Hendrix's death on September 18th 1970, this film tells Jimi Hendrix's life story in his own words and is narrated by funk legend Bootsy Collins in the soft, authoritative voice of Hendrix himself. Blending archive footage, artefacts, news archive and rare performance footage, director Bob Smeaton's film takes us from Hendrix's childhood in Seattle, through his spell in the army and on to his time on the chitlin circuit backing the likes of the Isley Brothers and Little Richard, his 'discovery' by ex-Animal Chas Chandler in New York, the formation of the Experience in the UK and his launch and instant popstardom in London in 1966, his stellar festival appearances at Monterey and Woodstock, his artistic progression, his last British concert at the end of August 1970 at the Isle of Wight Festival and his tragic death in Notting Hill, choked on his own vomit and red wine.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221126234500 +0000" stop="20221127004500 +0000" catchup-id="pQLWZM8L5tluSQ2yq6jskP5R30Jls0wcx0xsfPhn"><title>The Misinvestigations of Romesh Ranganathan : Jimi Hendrix</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Romesh Ranganathan – a comedian with admittedly no experience of criminal investigations whatsoever – attempts to resolve the mysterious death of Jimi Hendrix, the maverick guitarist who was found dead in a Notting Hill flat in September 1970.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127004500 +0000" stop="20221127014500 +0000" catchup-id="laIqVb_9bh2EBOeUeF_rCBnmQ3gdYrt9McwRCm9S"><title>Totally 60s Psychedelic Rock at the BBC</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>A compilation from the depths of the BBC archive of the creme de la creme of 1960s British psychedelic rock from programmes such as Colour Me Pop, How It Is, Top of the Pops and Once More with Felix. Featuring pre-rocker era Status Quo, a rustic-looking Incredible String Band, a youthful Donovan, a suitably eccentric performance from The Bonzo Dog Doo Dah Band, a trippy routine from Julie Driscoll, Brian Auger &amp; The Trinity, a groovy tune from The Moody Blues, a raucous rendition by Joe Cocker of his version of With a Little Help From My Friends and some pre-Wizzard Roy Wood with The Move. Plus classic performances from the likes of Procol Harum, Cream, Jimi Hendrix and The Who.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127014500 +0000" stop="20221127032000 +0000" catchup-id="gFWRJ2XYJAlp2clYaP0iesQ9UkJV92SV8WHt3t6S"><title>Father John Misty at 6 Music Festival</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Father John Misty's performance at St David's Hall, Cardiff, from the BBC 6 Music Festival in April 2022.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127032000 +0000" stop="20221127042000 +0000" catchup-id="YxXWf3KeOHs0XnhNs2LVv7oJ7kL-W4QpW6C9tEYQ"><title>Celebrity Antiques Road Trip</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/5_Dul6Lg_CFLFmGN6Ods1Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Breaking news - today’s star-studded shopping spree features award-winning journalist and newscaster Nina Hossain, along with fellow reporter Lucrezia Millarini. This pair of newsies are driving a custard-coloured 1955 Ford Pop Hot Rod, with expert advice provided by Dorset’s Tim Medhurst and Geordie-boy Steven Moore, who are piloting a 1960s Ford Thames between the antique shops and emporia. Their shopping bonanza between Nottinghamshire and Derbyshire will end with an ‘and finally’ at an auction in Buckinghamshire. Along the way Nina and Steven will learn about the unique Derbyshire tradition of well dressing, while Lucrezia and Tim find out about an invention which heralded the industrial revolution. Nina finds a love letter from the past and a silver brooch, while Lucrezia finds a jewellery casket that features a monkey riding an elephant – an item that’s sure to make big news at auction.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127042000 +0000" stop="20221127061500 +0000" catchup-id="gS4IfkV4Qr8kIQw6a3lu3ciN2rgxvXnnzDhlNCBX"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127061500 +0000" stop="20221127070000 +0000" catchup-id="gJBtRw9oPHOabiJxdCVaSECzqw78b6vWBqeGlm5K"><title>Countryfile : Plant Britain Finale</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/OmIgbtzITYU0rcuGfMFGUg.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127070000 +0000" stop="20221127080000 +0000" catchup-id="KaxbjcrDnxLLV3Q59tykVZEH7lTOy0vm8FetR7Si"><title>The Wild Gardener</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/YpuuHJyAScWW8Y2FQPoFEA.jpg"></icon><desc>Wildlife cameraman Colin Stafford-Johnson returns home to Ireland on a personal quest to transform his old childhood garden into a haven for native wildlife.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127080000 +0000" stop="20221127083000 +0000" catchup-id="N0LYbEdOgCp9jgxq7re6jAjYDG4Prz2NH8ywA6ul"><title>Beechgrove Gardens in Winter</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>George Anderson and Calum Clunie round off the series of autumn and winter gardening advice from Beechgrove. They answer viewers’ questions on topics covering the gardening jobs that need to get done between now and the spring, and there is a report from father and daughter Erin and Joe Armstrong from their plot in East Lothian. Calum is back on his own plot at Beechgrove this week, planting bare root roses and moving a rhubarb crown, he also checks on the tatties he planted that should be ready for Christmas dinner. There’s also a report from another gorgeous garden that the show featured during the summer to find out what they are up to at this time of year.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127083000 +0000" stop="20221127090000 +0000" catchup-id="i9AbFoI6T-kaPLWKWi7Azn3PXUOcMbbsPjPBtJOP"><title>Landward</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/u3Db7sHjg7elQb5gbijcKg.jpg"></icon><desc>Dougie and the team make the 100-mile journey from the mainland out into the Atlantic to discover St Kilda, Britain's remotest and wildest islands. Dougie takes a walk up the highest sea cliffs in Britain and gets a bird's-eye view of the geology and ecology. He hears worrying evidence that the world-renowned seabirds' colonies are now facing an uncertain future due to climate change. Elsewhere, Anne follows the last islanders, discovering why these Hebridean people eventually had to leave. She also discovers what the hundreds of unique structures that are scattered throughout the islands were used for. Meanwhile, Cammy finds out about the ancient sheep population and why they are so fascinating for scientists. He also goes behind the scenes to see the seasonal ranger's home and finds out what it's like to live full-time on St Kilda.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127090000 +0000" stop="20221127100000 +0000" catchup-id="eMnNi6TgfblZCGxqFm6OQRWULQayN_h0H28gHNdv"><title>This Farming Life</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/Ze4YmpYL_uzFB0C4cNvB_w.jpg"></icon><desc>Summer turns to autumn in Bute, Emma and Ewan are in the market for new tups or rams to produce good prime lambs the following spring. When they arrive at Kelso, the biggest sheep market in Europe, one pen in particular catches that their eye belongs to none other than Mike from Collessie Farm in Fife. Prices are high, but they can’t afford to come away empty-handed. Later in Fife, Mike puts in a shift at the family’s feed business, delivering animal feed to customers all over Fife. Meanwhile, in Orkney, Sean’s dad is preparing to drive hundreds of miles with his tups to one of the last sales of the year in Carlisle. It’s the Autumn Equinox, and the ferry crossing is rough. Back home, Sean has figured out a new way to sell from the island, joining the 52 per cent of farmers now buying and selling online.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127100000 +0000" stop="20221127113000 +0000" catchup-id="PTY7FUxkuo_aGPq_mbs-T5U-ZhY10TU0XZTPvInq"><title>Saturday Kitchen Best Bites</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/RP_5PKqX4rIMk-YZUlBkXg.jpg"></icon><desc>Matt Tebbutt takes a look back at some of his favourite recipes and best moments from Saturday Kitchen.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127113000 +0000" stop="20221127123000 +0000" catchup-id="VqvE4YCQD-n7sCuTvYC_LQSeKiOV0bl8uWImM5Xp"><title>Mary Berry's Country House Secrets : Scone Palace</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/4L5RrWwkY0umC6XvDHMVpg.jpg"></icon><desc>Mary visits Scone Palace, the crowning place of Scottish kings and the epicentre of Scottish history, where she is invited to help Lady Mansfield prepare for a special dinner with traditional Scottish reeling in the palace where Prince Albert and Queen Victoria were once amused. Mary enjoys salmon fishing on the family's private stretch of the Tay, and the regal pastime of Highland deer stalking with William, the future Earl of Mansfield, as well as the family's long-serving gamekeeper. Inspired by such royal history, Mary rustles up Scottish classics in the estate kitchen, including venison wellington, cock-a-leekie soup and cranachan.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127123000 +0000" stop="20221127130000 +0000" catchup-id="LJHuL83_2aNqOgVdxxr1ltT6RRbtUD3DbyDF3K7s"><title>Recipes That Made Me : Bangladesh</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Restaurateur Nisha Katona travels around the UK meeting home cooks to discover family recipes passed down through generations from across the Indian subcontinent. In this episode, Nisha travels to Greater Manchester to meet incredible home cooks from the Bangladeshi community. Eight out of ten restaurants referred to as Indian across the UK are actually owned by Bangladeshis, so Nisha starts her exploration into this cuisine in one of the many Bangladeshi-run curry houses in this area.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127130000 +0000" stop="20221127143000 +0000" catchup-id="rrHqU3RVOXtMfu1hO7rfCaOUys5i63FDEG2rK5vs"><title>School for Scoundrels</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>British comedy about a born loser who enrols at the College of Lifemanship and turns his life around by learning how to charm and cheat his way to the top with the minimum of effort. Adapted from the Oneupmanship books by Stephen Potter</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127143000 +0000" stop="20221127155000 +0000" catchup-id="_AVIxuBInk5CgRY_Sb7kgmxv4Y6dJGDIXsxDu1_q"><title>The Titfield Thunderbolt</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/ZVPzJghNO2qy_pltn_7ATA.jpg"></icon><desc>Ealing comedy about a group of villagers and their battle to preserve the local railway line by running it themselves, an enterprise that goes well until they are sabotaged in a midnight raid by the rival bus company. Undaunted, they wheel out the Thunderbolt, an ancient exhibit in the village museum. Now all that remains is to put on a satisfactory run for the stickler of a government inspector</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127155000 +0000" stop="20221127165000 +0000" catchup-id="DuHRN2GDUaqbrZh0SlM_cfKeCdvgX06UleThrl0H"><title>Locomotion: Dan Snow's History of Railways</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/eUod9YzjGnWVoJqtcRxCJw.jpg"></icon><desc>Documentary series. From their beginnings as a primitive system of track-ways for coal carts in the early 18th century, railways quickly developed into the driving force behind the industrial revolution and the pivotal technology for modern Britain. Rapid industrial growth during the early 19th century, coupled with the prospect of vast profits, drove inventors and entrepreneurs to develop steam locomotives, metal tracks and an array of daring tunnels, cuttings and bridges that created a nationwide system of railways in just 30 years. George Stephenson's Liverpool and Manchester Railway became the model for future inter-city travel for the next century and his fast, reliable locomotive, the Rocket, began a quest for speed that has defined our modern world.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127165000 +0000" stop="20221127173000 +0000" catchup-id="DNrDA6LfXdUI_ibpK20b4buxocPotiPLFM6p3hfo"><title>Flog It! : Guildford 23</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc>This Flog It! comes from Guildford Cathedral, one of the few cathedrals to be built in the 20th century. Presenter Paul Martin is joined by experts James Lewis and Mark Stacey, and together they hunt for interesting antiques and collectables to be sold at a local auction. Finds include an unusual piece of modern art and a Lalique vase which was bought at a car boot sale. But which will do better when they go under the hammer? Paul takes a look at the role music has played in the church and has a go at bell ringing.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127173000 +0000" stop="20221127183000 +0000" catchup-id="fe7KtpvSpq9m3m616ZsOQ2sAC8gLbD5V8Xzl21Ry"><title>This Farming Life</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/Ze4YmpYL_uzFB0C4cNvB_w.jpg"></icon><desc>At Corrimony Farm in Loch Ness, pumpkin season finally arrives. The Girvan family put on the largest pick-a-pumpkin event the glen has ever seen, just in time for Halloween. Further down the glen, Donald and Joanna play catch-up after losing two weeks to Covid. Meanwhile, at Bridge of Aird Dairy in Stranraer, calving season is in full flow. Kayleigh works alongside dad Andy to save a cow that has come down with milk fever, before completing her last shift in the milking parlour. And in Bute, Emma and Ewan put their new tups out into the field, and while their attention is on the sheep, George the bull manages to trample through one of their new gates.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127183000 +0000" stop="20221127193000 +0000" catchup-id="C4P9UiKVxj0AZlmYYpSK161zadimnnUtY-82WwtF"><title>Countryfile : Inclusive Farming</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/OmIgbtzITYU0rcuGfMFGUg.jpg"></icon><desc>Matt Baker and Sean Fletcher roll up their sleeves to help out on a remarkable smallholding in Bedfordshire. Farmer Mike Duxbury lost his sight at the age of six due to glaucoma, but that didn’t stop him from achieving his dream to farm. Touch and sound enable him to navigate the farm and take on anything that needs doing, from checking livestock to wielding power tools to build animal enclosures. And Mike is determined to inspire young people with disabilities to get into agriculture by running practical courses. Meanwhile, Joe Crowley investigates if enough is being done to combat wildlife crime, and Adam Henson catches up with a farmer who nearly lost his livelihood due to injury.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127193000 +0000" stop="20221127201500 +0000" catchup-id="g3o-fibSTeCbGilga65NYtT00HJ0GOgUA_DBRmkY"><title>Stanley Tucci: Searching for Italy : Liguria</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/B-tgVt8AdBGQOtDdTH5n4Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Stanley Tucci visits one of the most famous and frequented regions of Italy, the Italian Riviera, for the glitz and glamour of Portofino and the stunning picture-perfect fishing villages of the Cinque Terre. Liguria is a thin strip of mountainous land, sandwiched between the Alps and the Apennines and lined with rugged scenery and stunning coastal views. Its capital, Genoa, was once a wealthy merchant empire, and now offers such rich cuisine as personalised stamped pasta and its most internationally acclaimed export, Genoese pesto. Tucci discovers how Ligurians have learned to adapt to life in this difficult landscape and how they have found ingenious solutions to survive and thrive.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127201500 +0000" stop="20221127211500 +0000" catchup-id="o975GndQiCU5bBeV-P3_oV1jzJMBA8wxAXPih1Rl"><title>Antiques Roadshow : Windermere Jetty 1</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/3bzLUHsDZ7qzi7YPXgOBzg.jpg"></icon><desc>Fiona Bruce and the team are at Windermere Jetty Museum in the Lake District, where finds include a valuable collection of silver trophies awarded to a pioneering woman sailor, a James Bond poster scraped off a wall, a guitar rescued from a skip, a wooden dinghy from the film Swallows and Amazons, and a pair of ‘lost’ necklaces with surprising values. Fiona finds out about the daredevils who have attempted to set speed records on the lakes.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127211500 +0000" stop="20221127221600 +0000" catchup-id="EQjs_0oNMqg3XdUzJhioTu9N-VLwpTXvscEHBLF_"><title>Simon Schama's History of Now : Truth and Democracy</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Simon Schama explores how artists and writers have led the fight for truth and democracy in his lifetime, often at great personal cost. Featuring Ai Weiwei and Nadya Tolokonnikova.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127221600 +0000" stop="20221127234000 +0000" catchup-id="Pu7ynl4aZAlvs7HS5eq8pIr6SXoBRatcwWQv8KaA"><title>Mogul Mowgli</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/lfSbX1TXmWvYnOtF5904oQ.jpg"></icon><desc>When his manager tells him that he has been booked to support a major tour, British-Pakistani rapper Zed believes it is going to be his break into the big time. Going home to Wembley to prepare and catch up with his family, he is suddenly struck by a debilitating illness that threatens to derail his lifetime ambition.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127234000 +0000" stop="20221127235500 +0000" catchup-id="aDhyr_RpKdGIxnez9fQinvU34cKsmUK08dNVR4Ri"><title>Expensive Sh*t</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>In a Glasgow nightclub, Tolu, a Nigerian toilet attendant desperate for survival, manipulates the behaviour of unsuspecting women for the titillation of men watching behind the mirrors. But tonight, a line has been crossed, and as the night spins out of control, Tolu has to find the strength to change everything.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221127235500 +0000" stop="20221128003000 +0000" catchup-id="cIMOheRS8H1omrZHT8T7piybkVU3EshxXBARcOA6"><title>Wet Leg at 6 Music Festival</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Wet Leg's set from the Great Hall in Cardiff during the BBC 6 Music Festival in April 2022.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128003000 +0000" stop="20221128010500 +0000" catchup-id="eBNn8FRpfByoJ4U1xpVfcoU9UZoakFSIZEgoIp-4"><title>QI : Television</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/mWzi8A0HiCWq5DjM2FsZkQ.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128010500 +0000" stop="20221128020500 +0000" catchup-id="vu6QtGvrK0BFT3TPj3mOGMDYKUqU4ij-o6-9_HeT"><title>Signed: Question Time</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/QsmtxqlGZlxjGLxPYGJ_4w.jpg"></icon><desc>Fiona Bruce presents an hour of debate from Skipton in North Yorkshire. On the panel, Conservative roads minister, Richard Holden MP; Labour’s Andy Burnham, who is a former cabinet minister, and now mayor of Greater Manchester; Charlotte Ivers, political correspondent at Times Radio; the former Brexit MEP and businessman, Ben Habib; and the author, musician and social commentator Darren McGarvey.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128020500 +0000" stop="20221128030500 +0000" catchup-id="tbUTRJFouQgfGforR4uPjw9AHiDIlOc0z4QBg0hz"><title>Signed: Ambulance</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/JbsgWPK_AY6vsONGYecFWA.jpg"></icon><desc>Chris and Iqra respond to an urgent 999 call for a suicidal patient who is struggling to pay the bills amid the increasing cost of living crisis.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128030500 +0000" stop="20221128061500 +0000" catchup-id="irRTF7lwqRo-ISWiA4Yz94MjvZqpNmkWb6y7fUeO"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128061500 +0000" stop="20221128071500 +0000" catchup-id="27BugS5ZygzMgYa4jOnXSt7eYxvlrtH6N8BZ4Eg9"><title>Homes Under the Hammer</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/Honvrz_XaSQZKyAyWRd86w.jpg"></icon><desc>We head back to the Norfolk village of Hilgay, where Tommy first saw a characterful semi-detached cottage with very low ceilings back at the beginning of 2022. He’s also in Southampton to see a two-bed end-terrace. Dion is in Stoke-on-Trent to see a three-bed semi in need of a layout change downstairs.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128071500 +0000" stop="20221128080000 +0000" catchup-id="D5GVSvqd4A04j72cK6po9xEpRYGz1ZSwSqpFiW8m"><title>Bargain Hunt : Builth Wells 3</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/_n4I9rQNXfb1yt_rdabD_Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Natasha Raskin Sharp and the teams shop for antiques in the market town of Builth Wells, with experts Ben Cooper and Kate Bliss on hand to help them sniff out the best bargains. While the teams are busy shopping, Natasha quizzes fairgoers about a mystery item.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128080000 +0000" stop="20221128090000 +0000" catchup-id="Jx99erPRAUiM5r7lx45LqAVJwWEa6kxGAoXL3zhF"><title>Signed: MasterChef: The Professionals</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/9iEXf-1bVLUoRAvPsDSWxA.jpg"></icon><desc>Four more chefs face Skills Tests set by Anna and Marcus. Two must prepare a pork chop with butter bean stew, while the other two cook tempura vegetables with nori seasoning.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128090000 +0000" stop="20221128100000 +0000" catchup-id="EHoFX9Zn82XJKYSpft9rGVqebl2dx63JxMK2dEkt"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/O4C25N7vCNk5hoXbwDrnIw.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest headlines, breaking news and sport from the BBC newsroom.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128100000 +0000" stop="20221128120000 +0000" catchup-id="jPitzoQBwZawe_03XcmKhTyEN6qYSzy9cc7__ojl"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/O4C25N7vCNk5hoXbwDrnIw.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128120000 +0000" stop="20221128124500 +0000" catchup-id="p94mQq64SExHXm3XzWiEQcUsPPVUga87ZrSIbw7m"><title>Bargain Hunt : Edinburgh 16</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/_n4I9rQNXfb1yt_rdabD_Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Natasha Raskin Sharp is in charge of proceedings at the Royal Highland Centre in Edinburgh as the reds and blues have 60 minutes to buy three items with £300. Helping to make sure the teams make a profit, experts Roo Irvine and David Harper are ready to spend the leftover lolly on a bonus buy.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128124500 +0000" stop="20221128133000 +0000" catchup-id="KWdZ9Bj_PM6OLrt2o2SjnmWYljdchS_E1W2he4_Z"><title>Politics Live</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The big political issues of the day.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128133000 +0000" stop="20221128134500 +0000" catchup-id="a8shN7sSPDR6TlRPsGpcIYFOXvJpQW6yIXYJw0e-"><title>The A-Z of TV Cooking : Letter A</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Masterchef's John Torode sifts through the archives and serves up a selection of mouthwatering dishes from some of the nation's favourite television chefs, starting with recipes and ingredients linked by the letter A.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128134500 +0000" stop="20221128141500 +0000" catchup-id="F1g1Tw5VbkhMm_A2RYV00ktRfVnSnswfaNU6Mz7s"><title>Eggheads</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/kxjywN32Sf7ZLWFid1pwVQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Jeremy Vine hosts the show where every day a new team of challengers take on probably the greatest quiz team in Britain. Can the challengers triumph or will the cash prize roll over to the next show?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128141500 +0000" stop="20221128144500 +0000" catchup-id="Srsfl1ynYbkD1zOlI3AeHe6dEXPOACTE5TqMWFLX"><title>Eggheads</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/kxjywN32Sf7ZLWFid1pwVQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Jeremy Vine hosts the show where every day a new team of challengers take on probably the greatest quiz team in Britain. Can the challengers triumph or will the cash prize roll over to the next show?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128144500 +0000" stop="20221128151500 +0000" catchup-id="NQNBcWxCK4nZbaGabWlODHzFC4DrVSQsimrAxjj_"><title>Fish Town</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/A3KxsSlg81R09sW1uc7BbA.jpg"></icon><desc>The Reliance's skipper John Clarke reflects on the future of his son, who is hoping to take over from him one day.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128151500 +0000" stop="20221128161500 +0000" catchup-id="1gligq9PxBir3193P1mlRWCPF_KF2lxBYFF25NzO"><title>The Great British Sewing Bee</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/aeXGrUG_zgu6O3cvo613-Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Joe Lycett hosts as the eight remaining home sewers return to the nation's most famous sewing room for children's week. The garments might be tiny, but their fiddliness makes them a mammoth challenge to sew. To test the sewers' dexterity, judges Patrick Grant and Esme Young kick off the Pattern Challenge with a classic for any toddler's wardrobe - a romper suit. The task requires the sewers to combine tricky techniques, including crossover straps, an elasticated back and, most difficult of all, snap fastenings at the crotch. Next, in the Transformation Challenge, the sewers let their imaginations run wild, turning adult wet suits into Under the Sea-themed fancy dress for children. Finally, the Sewing Bee welcomes mini-models for the Made to Measure challenge, which is to make a child's raincoat. These must be well fitted, allowing enough movement for jumping up and down in muddy puddles, whilst also being fully waterproof. Who will win Garment of the Week, and who will stumble, becomi</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128161500 +0000" stop="20221128171500 +0000" catchup-id="7A8Tc-BtD3EhwAHoJMf1V4Eafurcflwb5OHdcOs2"><title>Locomotion: Dan Snow's History of Railways</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/az1nncopZjETu98i-AllYQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Documentary series tracing the development of Britain's railways. In the late 1830s the railways arrived in London and linked the capital to Birmingham, Liverpool and Manchester. This was the start of a truly national network and one of the greatest civil engineering projects in history. The railways triggered a mania across Britain. Railway tycoons like Samuel Morton Peto and George Hudson made fortunes as the stock markets boomed. But the bubble burst in 1847 and shares plummeted. Thousands of ordinary shareholders filled the bankruptcy courts. Yet as Dan Snow reveals, the legacy of the mania was an incredible rail network and a revolution in the way people lived</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128171500 +0000" stop="20221128180000 +0000" catchup-id="vhc41YL2r7eTm9SNysf6qtSGhhvhz4kItEgXq3iO"><title>Flog It! : Rochester Cathedral 25</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128180000 +0000" stop="20221128183000 +0000" catchup-id="NYcCvRXQUlo5zDdNa54pCRzB-xOe1cobNHWE6eWk"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games : Week 13: Monday</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/QTvvZ81udNlpPp2OS-TMAQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Every day this week, former winners Stephen Bailey, Charlie Brooks, Ria Lina and John Thomson take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Facing their second chance to win a prize, will the winning stars opt for the House of Games golden goblets, or will they be tempted with the must-have House of Games golden fondue set?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128183000 +0000" stop="20221128190000 +0000" catchup-id="C-2iVwYV1_9HU46iumLcRhmJLgjy0q9bjuoNLVu6"><title>Strictly It Takes Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/jBI3R8x1LdHWuBnckASH_A.jpg"></icon><desc>Janette Manrara chats exclusively to the latest couple to be eliminated from the competition. With more interviews and backstage gossip in the run up to Musicals Week.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128190000 +0000" stop="20221128193000 +0000" catchup-id="rmNpkbFlLbVqAtj_lz_YglMltNl4_B5GPHgu4217"><title>FA Cup : 3rd Round Draw</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/Vh2bT7iLAXrXRK_pw9pXrA.jpg"></icon><desc>Anticipation is palpable around the country as lower and non-league clubs and their fans discover whether they get a glamour tie against Premier League opponents. The third-round draw is an annual institution, with the Premier League and Championship sides joining the FA Cup at this stage – it ensures the plucking of each team’s number from a bowl becomes compulsive viewing.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128193000 +0000" stop="20221128200000 +0000" catchup-id="b6qabslfyyrCJPqcSj8cDGbJs3vi5hbB3bzO2_SW"><title>Mastermind</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/2x2bAg5oZd-Vt9Cw9pfaCw.jpg"></icon><desc>Clive Myrie hosts as another four contenders take to the black chair, answering questions on their chosen specialist subjects to earn a place in the semi-finals. The specialist subjects are Michael Palin's travel documentaries, Lady Gaga, Emily Dickinson and the BBC sitcom Mum.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128200000 +0000" stop="20221128203000 +0000" catchup-id="raN14BBGDCg9KZTIekIc8Oyyeo2yTpVV2wj3l9Vf"><title>Only Connect : Mothers Ruined v Cryptics</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/-dwHFg_l7ZoJCCwKGGBPXQ.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128203000 +0000" stop="20221128210000 +0000" catchup-id="qBdKJjxvIujxN6V4DoQMfV9VeiVGkQoBwJDr5VmV"><title>University Challenge</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/DthQg2qIu4T3wO2ltne1Hg.jpg"></icon><desc>In the last of the first-round matches, Robert Gordon University return to the competition for the first time in 28 years to face the University of Roehampton, appearing for the first time ever. Jeremy Paxman asks the questions.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128210000 +0000" stop="20221128220000 +0000" catchup-id="L6FRXLNToyXwRHyqRe4zkM35OIWeuHrF-JW-gWF_"><title>Trailblazers: A Rocky Mountain Road Trip</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Three generations of trailblazing women - Ruby Wax, Melanie Brown and Emily Atack - come together to retrace the famous footsteps of intrepid Victorian explorer Isabella Bird. Travelling alone, Isabella crossed the lawless American Wild West, riding 800 miles on horseback through the Rocky Mountains of Colorado. She befriended outlaws, climbed mountains, and faced grizzly bears in what was a restrictive era for women in Britain. Using her original 1873 book A Lady's Life in the Rocky Mountains as inspiration for their own adventure, Ruby, Mel and Emily want to pay homage to this forgotten pioneer. They explore the people, places and curious customs of an ever-changing America, while reflecting on the changes in western society over the last 150 years and their own experiences of womanhood.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128220000 +0000" stop="20221128223000 +0000" catchup-id="d1Ait1yEB-Ft7JWtieYFdhY7TudOart5aqDVzKgd"><title>Motherland : School Trip</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/AGdgUx6IAsgiJvz6TSPeKA.jpg"></icon><desc>It's time for the Year 6 school trip, and Julia, Liz and Meg find themselves on the coach journey from hell with humourless school secretary Mrs Lamb and clueless teaching assistant Ms Vaughn. It all kicks off when a boy banned for bad behaviour is allowed on the coach along with his mother Ashley, and Liz decides to play the hero. Meanwhile, Kevin takes his driving test, and Amanda pivots her lifestyle brand Hygge Tygge online. She manages to persuade Kevin to help pack up the shop - with unimaginable consequences.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128223000 +0000" stop="20221128231500 +0000" catchup-id="9Mv3vsQRF9pZByZNMwehZLSKxKsaV_0fGilkwMTQ"><title>Newsnight</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bUQ-JbBOx1dTvpjQEinXPw.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Kirsty Wark.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221128231500 +0000" stop="20221129005000 +0000" catchup-id="tviKf66uGH72Pjo4WLI_FHE-0evl0jzsi1YPXAhp"><title>The Wife</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/ZpDVDrrCnyNjVzJFo1wDLQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Successful writer Joe Castleman is delighted to receive an early morning telephone call from Sweden informing him that he has won this year's Nobel Prize for Literature. His steadfast wife Joan is equally delighted, but as she prepares to travel to Stockholm to support and encourage her husband, she reflects on her life from when she first met Joe, her married literature tutor with whom she embarks on the affair which would change the course of their lives.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129005000 +0000" stop="20221129015000 +0000" catchup-id="Af4ho8AWmfG5IjkixKTKDMqEB1dC8eprOz09_Cos"><title>Simon Schama's History of Now : Truth and Democracy</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Simon Schama explores how artists and writers have led the fight for truth and democracy in his lifetime, often at great personal cost. Featuring Ai Weiwei and Nadya Tolokonnikova.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129015000 +0000" stop="20221129023500 +0000" catchup-id="Qj82csokmyF1iHDknkGD-VTqr1hWtZ_oAjpPWbOh"><title>Signed: Countryfile : Plant Britain Finale</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/OmIgbtzITYU0rcuGfMFGUg.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129023500 +0000" stop="20221129033500 +0000" catchup-id="IDTjBqh3ci0u1pYeEvpiY-wzzjK2P7vrCGYqJs-Y"><title>Signed: The Secret Genius of Modern Life : Bank Card</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Hannah Fry takes a look at the bank card. This humble piece of plastic is often taken for granted, but it’s the digital key to accessing cash and is packed full of extraordinary technological innovations - including some with surprising and sinister origins. Hannah is granted the first ever TV access to Visa’s European bank card data centre, discovers why we have Russian spies to thank for contactless payments, and finds out how the CIA and a 1950s housewife helped kick-start the bank card revolution.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129033500 +0000" stop="20221129063000 +0000" catchup-id="Jc8FzlJl4gVWIONYkDhBiLOZxPpZLOlahoPV6X2E"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129063000 +0000" stop="20221129071500 +0000" catchup-id="W6C-Fz0pCMSFLCtUPmGRDAB5OqcoeSMT9yn9IcmH"><title>Money for Nothing</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7QssTsRrKA7Ad2b5d9jQFw.jpg"></icon><desc>Sarah Moore is at Witley recycling centre on a mission to stop three unwanted items being crushed. She intercepts a collection of hessian sacks, four dining chairs and some wooden drawers and a rug. With the help of bag-maker Rosanna Gethin and upholsterer Ollie Clueit, Sarah hopes to give new life to the old items, but will she harvest any profits by selling them on?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129071500 +0000" stop="20221129080000 +0000" catchup-id="xkICpX0Ha3maGlAZFolY_i0gRreGISniYHezqWyu"><title>Escape to the Country : Cornwall</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/3oX-Fb_En1VQaDIMqBzT9w.jpg"></icon><desc>Denise Nurse is in the coastal county of Cornwall today, helping a couple to turn their favourite holiday destination into their permanent home on a budget of £475,000. Away from the search, Denise visits a new development that’s tackling the county’s housing crisis by prioritising the needs of local Cornish people.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129080000 +0000" stop="20221129090000 +0000" catchup-id="GugjsRgjNMlPHyjltz57G4RbRzEXIw7SQrYzD5Of"><title>Signed: MasterChef: The Professionals</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/9iEXf-1bVLUoRAvPsDSWxA.jpg"></icon><desc>The hunt for the champion continues as four new chefs set out to prove they are serious contenders for the MasterChef: The Professionals crown. Two chefs must prove they have what it takes in a Skills Test set by Anna Haugh. They have just 20 minutes to make sweet potato gnocchi with a hazelnut pesto. The other two face Marcus Wareing's test, which involves a dish of poached apricots and chantilly cream with an almond tuile. Then all four cook off against each other in the Signature Menu round. This is their chance to showcase what their cooking is all about with recipes of their own design. Only the two most talented contenders will make it through to the quarter-final and continue their pursuit of the MasterChef: The Professionals trophy.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129090000 +0000" stop="20221129100000 +0000" catchup-id="5YMdKgulwjjBIFxDVWNjYwEpZIgOKi3Eoo7MK6Mx"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/O4C25N7vCNk5hoXbwDrnIw.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest headlines, breaking news and sport from the BBC newsroom.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129100000 +0000" stop="20221129121500 +0000" catchup-id="FqAQ71HbKge_aiQOHGPO8HIQFPOXLklgAN6mUn8c"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/O4C25N7vCNk5hoXbwDrnIw.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129121500 +0000" stop="20221129130000 +0000" catchup-id="wGghg-Ennc0KG8DxKeM4A7WVhZfAWxgC5E8ABovS"><title>Politics Live</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The big political issues of the day.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129130000 +0000" stop="20221129134500 +0000" catchup-id="nxiWwhPAON2c8iufVspWEwvnaIZRU6ozmADFPdKO"><title>Flipping Profit</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>An antiques expert, a market trader and an upcycler battle it out to make the most money for BBC Children in Need. In this episode, art valuer Kate Bliss, mouthy trader Danny Sebastian and aeronautical engineer/upcycler Stu Abbott head to Ludlow to rummage through its antique shops, scrap yards and flea markets in the hope of finding items that they can each turn into a healthy profit. When the day is done and they've got their items, they have just three weeks to turn them into cash. Who can grab the most cash for their dressmakers dummies, Danny or Kate? Has Stu bitten off more than he can chew with his ambitious designs? It's a race to sell, sell, sell before the time is up and their profits are revealed.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129134500 +0000" stop="20221129141500 +0000" catchup-id="wz0Emc8vnm8znBZTC-MmKdswIWdqjNgQwJjGU4uu"><title>Eggheads</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/kxjywN32Sf7ZLWFid1pwVQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Jeremy Vine hosts the show where every day a new team of challengers take on probably the greatest quiz team in Britain. Can the challengers triumph or will the cash prize roll over to the next show?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129141500 +0000" stop="20221129144500 +0000" catchup-id="ptnY9lWE98OwPFYVClqw3jtrX1ZMNXUNpYpr051L"><title>Eggheads</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/kxjywN32Sf7ZLWFid1pwVQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Jeremy Vine hosts the show where every day a new team of challengers take on probably the greatest quiz team in Britain. Can the challengers triumph or will the cash prize roll over to the next show?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129144500 +0000" stop="20221129151500 +0000" catchup-id="2heiUOfBFL51t6_m809Zt17nPOnOYBGvWxUj8Ncv"><title>Fish Town</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/A3KxsSlg81R09sW1uc7BbA.jpg"></icon><desc>James Cosmo narrates a six-part series about the UK's biggest fishing port, Peterhead in north east Scotland. Fishing boat the Boy John sets out from Peterhead harbour in search of whitefish in the remote Norwegian sector of the North Sea. However, the catches are poor and skipper Jonny McLeman feels the pressure. The crew are relieved when the net looks heavy but discover they have caught a huge rock. The Zenith sets out in search of whitefish and prawns with 28-year-old Paul Robertson at thge helm and his 26-year-old brother Adam in charge of the deck. They start with a good catch but the hauls begin to get smaller, leaving Paul with a tough decision to make. Back on land, at Peterhead's busy fish market, quality advisor Allison Sherrington does her rounds at the early-morning sale. A big change is coming as the harbour authority has built a huge new state-of-the-art fishmarket as part of a £50m redevelopment, and it is Allison's job to make sure it opens on time.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129151500 +0000" stop="20221129161500 +0000" catchup-id="-_zT1cgKtUQZSSynNRTEY9ZYw3Qa95AXWKC5NqvQ"><title>The Great British Sewing Bee : Reduce, Reuse and Recycle Week</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/e9sEgrAgWBGr4b9-nE90Ig.jpg"></icon><desc>The fashion industry is the biggest polluter of our planet next to oil, so The Great British Sewing Bee returns to Reduce, Reuse and Recycle Week, with all the usual fabric in the haberdashery being replaced with charity shop clothes and soft-furnishings. Host Joe Lycett kicks the six remaining home sewers off with a pattern for a gentleman's waistcoat using just second-hand clothes. In the Transformation Challenge, the sewers are tasked with changing items of army surplus into a stylish and wearable garment for a woman. Finally, the sewers are asked to use old jeans to create a Made to Measure dress. Jeans are one of the most polluting garments to manufacture, so to breathe a new lease of life into them, each sewer must create a new denim dress that fits their model perfectly. At the end, someone will win Garment of the Week, and a sixth sewer will be asked to leave the Sewing Bee.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129161500 +0000" stop="20221129171500 +0000" catchup-id="TaLe6Y5OKtz3Yba63ZwpyloFlAIQUiMcsq7sNTXD"><title>Locomotion: Dan Snow's History of Railways</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/f0tKqkANwlrriC6PrTuTMw.jpg"></icon><desc>Documentary series tracing the development of Britain's railways. Over just 50 years, Britain's railways grew from a handful of small lines carrying coal to the biggest industry in the strongest nation on the planet. A nation had built the railways and now those railways would build a nation, influencing working conditions for its employees, proving a valuable export across the globe and even changing warfare. Yet the story of railways up until the beginning of the Second World War concerned who they really belonged to - the private rail companies who were obsessed with profit, the public who rode them, or the government, who needed them at times of crisis but was reluctant to regulate</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129171500 +0000" stop="20221129174500 +0000" catchup-id="n2o34A9MTSEQRXtvC160tQo1tkmWv7Jowl72vZ9C"><title>Flog It! : Cheshire</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc>Paul Martin and experts Mark Stacey, Anita Manning and David Fletcher are at Tatton Park in Cheshire.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129174500 +0000" stop="20221129181500 +0000" catchup-id="j63Fq9YNO0Pk4oMnbwjOQ0Y1Kg98lS7txEocrINz"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games : Week 13: Tuesday</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/QTvvZ81udNlpPp2OS-TMAQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Every day this week, former winners Stephen Bailey, Charlie Brooks, Ria Lina and John Thomson take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Facing their second chance to win a prize, will the winning stars opt for the House of Games golden goblets, or will they be tempted with the must-have House of Games golden fondue set?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129181500 +0000" stop="20221129184500 +0000" catchup-id="fV4WLRQT-Ct58uvUTFqRnNAJOUj-H8kWVlVlPpCV"><title>Strictly It Takes Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/jBI3R8x1LdHWuBnckASH_A.jpg"></icon><desc>Janette Manrara is back with more backstage gossip and behind-the-scenes action from the world of Strictly. Plus, Choreography Corner dissects the performances from the weekend.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129184500 +0000" stop="20221129211000 +0000" catchup-id="FtAkoXcmujjAziNDEboNnixHCApj72z8wNH2xYFy"><title>FIFA World Cup : Iran v USA</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/XeomcJiZ2fh8-E0Eprht9A.jpg"></icon><desc>Gabby Logan introduces live World Cup action as Iran take on the USA at Al Thumama Stadium in the third and final round of matches in Group B. The Iranians have won only two matches at their previous five World Cups, including a famous first victory against the Americans at France 98. The USA failed to qualify for the 2018 tournament in Russia, but with a young and exciting squad of predominantly European-based players, expectations are high for head coach Gregg Berhalter and his players in Qatar. Commentary comes from Steve Wilson and Danny Murphy.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129211000 +0000" stop="20221129213000 +0000" catchup-id="ypFZ0-jsDHIsbFpDcU_VUGXSV22eDdQbkE1TcEuh"><title>What We Do in the Shadows : Resurrection</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/wf2Qt_a1ead1SZNXmwszbQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Nadja and Laszlo's new familiar poses problems for an increasingly anxious Guillermo, and the vampires enlist the services of a local necromancer.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129213000 +0000" stop="20221129221500 +0000" catchup-id="XyR_n9AjeUatr-1jhG4vYFeyjLtTjLKhkQbiuSJ2"><title>Louis Theroux Interviews... : Rita Ora</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Louis Theroux meets global popstar Rita Ora for a revealing conversation about her musical career, dealing with press scrutiny and her family’s arrival in the UK as refugees.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129221500 +0000" stop="20221129224500 +0000" catchup-id="ISOQCTE3N6c6IaY5ErRjhdK9L1eVBXVCDErfwQck"><title>Frankie Boyle's New World Order</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/Yt8fAoVbMGXYLN5kURdE1w.jpg"></icon><desc>Frankie Boyle returns to help make sense of this disconcerting time, tackling the biggest issues troubling the planet and making a string of bold and often outrageous statements, which he then picks apart with the help of Kiri Pritchard-McLean, Jamali Maddix, Susie McCabe and Christopher Macarthur-Boyd.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129224500 +0000" stop="20221129233000 +0000" catchup-id="kSkA8q710XF99-STnGpOUI0ZqWy5CjY8lHnO_Juh"><title>Newsnight</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bUQ-JbBOx1dTvpjQEinXPw.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Victoria Derbyshire.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221129233000 +0000" stop="20221130003000 +0000" catchup-id="FrIxOxocU_Pi0Jq0FU-rLAjGhehxzRtwcSCtIg0r"><title>Trailblazers: A Rocky Mountain Road Trip</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Three generations of trailblazing women - Ruby Wax, Melanie Brown and Emily Atack - come together to retrace the famous footsteps of intrepid Victorian explorer Isabella Bird. Travelling alone, Isabella crossed the lawless American Wild West, riding 800 miles on horseback through the Rocky Mountains of Colorado. She befriended outlaws, climbed mountains, and faced grizzly bears in what was a restrictive era for women in Britain. Using her original 1873 book A Lady's Life in the Rocky Mountains as inspiration for their own adventure, Ruby, Mel and Emily want to pay homage to this forgotten pioneer. They explore the people, places and curious customs of an ever-changing America, while reflecting on the changes in western society over the last 150 years and their own experiences of womanhood.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130003000 +0000" stop="20221130023000 +0000" catchup-id="HZHycDX3iecXxa-NoTWiObPSgMYaxvecIQT1Hlgf"><title>McFarland, USA</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/4W4uOiBuMW00oS9mibQn2A.jpg"></icon><desc>Sports drama based on a true story about a team of underdogs who chase success with the help of a failed American football coach. Led by Jim White, a group of Latino students with an exceptional talent for long-distance running learn about discipline and a good work ethic as they face adversity together and bid to become cross country champions.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130023000 +0000" stop="20221130031000 +0000" catchup-id="oc_fg3rFw1Nwg8R2nhlqSrlDc_yepHHNsocp-Th_"><title>Signed: Stanley Tucci: Searching for Italy : London</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/B-tgVt8AdBGQOtDdTH5n4Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Stanley Tucci sets out to explore how Italian immigration has transformed the food scene in his adopted hometown of London. London is a culinary mecca, where Italian food from every region gets a chance to shine. The burrata is so creamy, the pasta so fresh, that it may rival Italy itself. For over a century, Italians here have found inventive ways to create Italian food so impressive that it's enough to render Tucci speechless.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130031000 +0000" stop="20221130035500 +0000" catchup-id="BqZQElOp59v09zqhRtsTuSfE-ldQwsqEiA0xEfOt"><title>Signed: Best Bakes Ever</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>With Britain more obsessed than ever with baking, actress and cake expert Jane Asher brings together a selection of recipes from the nation's favourite television chefs, for Best Bakes Ever. Each episode gives baking fans another chance to experience classic dishes from the likes of the James Martin, Mary Berry and Paul Hollywood, the Hairy Bikers, Raymond Blanc, Nigella Lawson, Tom Kerridge, Lorraine Pascale and Rachel Khoo. There's added insight and appreciation from Jane herself too. Whether it's cakes, pies, puddings or main courses - this greatest hits of baking is a must for anyone with a need to knead, and should help inspire even more of us to start getting creative in the kitchen.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130035500 +0000" stop="20221130061500 +0000" catchup-id="2eCBZsyRLuefzEpSkVDnboG3G1d53YNLJdlT9mPa"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130061500 +0000" stop="20221130071500 +0000" catchup-id="i5_0-czp40lGIEiaq9FbpfieRFxRrOe65KS17NHw"><title>Homes Under the Hammer</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/Honvrz_XaSQZKyAyWRd86w.jpg"></icon><desc>It’s a tale of two detached bungalows for Tommy as he visits Mexborough in South Yorkshire and Orpington in London. Martel is in the village of Greengill in Cumbria to see a detached house set on several acres of rural land.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130071500 +0000" stop="20221130080000 +0000" catchup-id="Nr1ItRBgE6vAxHFXA_sxSHiUQDWwJK6zU8Y8iiHl"><title>Bargain Hunt : Ardingly 28</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/_n4I9rQNXfb1yt_rdabD_Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Charlie Ross and the teams try to uncover profitable antiques in Sussex with experts Caroline Hawley and Tim Weeks. While the reds and blues compete to make the most money at auction, Charlie learns how science can help to prove the authenticity of ancient artefacts, using a process called thermoluminescence.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130080000 +0000" stop="20221130090000 +0000" catchup-id="bAhvAxNylgUUJJXdOgejmFcVjPLUEmbWuHqVknCM"><title>Signed: MasterChef: The Professionals</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/9iEXf-1bVLUoRAvPsDSWxA.jpg"></icon><desc>The quarter-finalists must prepare dishes based around the combination of orange and ginger. Then they cook for food critics Tom Parker Bowles, Tracy MacLeod and Grace Dent.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130090000 +0000" stop="20221130100000 +0000" catchup-id="y6_3EwJMQ5KXbmj3XWtYXjJo5JIjae6eomt34zZy"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/O4C25N7vCNk5hoXbwDrnIw.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest headlines, breaking news and sport from the BBC newsroom.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130100000 +0000" stop="20221130111500 +0000" catchup-id="z3Rawl-cj-ScJrheMUTZgSIN21O9sjCvA1dQZ0cP"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/O4C25N7vCNk5hoXbwDrnIw.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130111500 +0000" stop="20221130130000 +0000" catchup-id="V3sQux_v9Vj6ywepPowUk-6yCjyBpyu0l28aX7dZ"><title>Politics Live</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The big political issues of the day.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130130000 +0000" stop="20221130134500 +0000" catchup-id="Y-RT8vsCxKC9cxSEmG9BKNT5_B-dQ4hsM7wNEXSQ"><title>Flipping Profit</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>An antiques expert, a market trader and an upcycler battle it out to make the most money for BBC Children in Need. In this episode, antiques auctioneer Charles Hanson, trader Linda Lambert and luxury upcycler Zoe Pocock head to Cambridge to rummage through its antique shops, scrap yards and flea markets in the hope of finding items that they can each turn into a healthy profit. When the day is done and they've got their items, they have just three weeks to turn them into cash. Will Charles find buyers for his Victorian Valentine's cards? Can Linda find a princess for her tiara? How will Zoe's sideboard turn out? It's all a rush as Zoe gets upcycling, Charles heads to auction and Linda goes to the theatre. At the end of the three weeks, who will be the king, or queen, of profit flippers?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130134500 +0000" stop="20221130141500 +0000" catchup-id="Ako3VsyzMFuKo3RFzdzpVekW8kcZg4t44u-lS8h4"><title>Eggheads</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/kxjywN32Sf7ZLWFid1pwVQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Jeremy Vine hosts the show where every day a new team of challengers take on probably the greatest quiz team in Britain. Can the challengers triumph or will the cash prize roll over to the next show?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130141500 +0000" stop="20221130144500 +0000" catchup-id="TgUx7boJuMqLc6Bp-dmCHfp7sc54KEeDlvqqdiFm"><title>Eggheads</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/kxjywN32Sf7ZLWFid1pwVQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Jeremy Vine hosts the show where every day a new team of challengers take on probably the greatest quiz team in Britain. Can the challengers triumph or will the cash prize roll over to the next show?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130144500 +0000" stop="20221130171500 +0000" catchup-id="o6NvnUyeNWsuJVLen-c8EX61vBODGgvyQvKT2yPM"><title>FIFA World Cup : Australia v Denmark</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/4VHCqOX713VnUn0_T04z2g.jpg"></icon><desc>Mark Chapman introduces live coverage as Australia take on Denmark at the Al Janoub Stadium in Qatar. The Socceroos have only reached the knockout round once prior to this World Cup, when they fell to Italy in the round of 16 in 2006. Denmark’s best run came back in 1998, when a side inspired by the likes of Brian Laudrup and Peter Schmeichel narrowly lost to Brazil in the quarter-finals. Commentary comes from Jonathan Pearce and Dion Dublin.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130171500 +0000" stop="20221130174500 +0000" catchup-id="aoEBTdNhFBhGLj381p7DV28oL4BqHKfwOv-OM1UQ"><title>Flog It! : Hereford</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc>Antiques series. Paul Martin experts Adam Partridge and Christina Trevanion are at Hereford Cathedral.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130174500 +0000" stop="20221130181500 +0000" catchup-id="8bmFHjP3KZ0U132oKIZ83awcfbFHmdf3TAwRrjZo"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games : Week 13: Wednesday</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/QTvvZ81udNlpPp2OS-TMAQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Every day this week, former winners Stephen Bailey, Charlie Brooks, Ria Lina and John Thomson take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Facing their second chance to win a prize, will the winning stars opt for the House of Games golden goblets, or will they be tempted with the must-have House of Games golden fondue set?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130181500 +0000" stop="20221130184500 +0000" catchup-id="278G8frIhYHoEFYPFAXXYDzA7thiWzrCQkCoSIue"><title>Strictly It Takes Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/jBI3R8x1LdHWuBnckASH_A.jpg"></icon><desc>Janette Manrara dishes up more backstage gossip and behind-the-scenes action from the world of Strictly.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130184500 +0000" stop="20221130211000 +0000" catchup-id="PypNGyzto_YDk3u2dj-MLx0L9DrcA9DN4UwYGhrP"><title>FIFA World Cup : Saudi Arabia v Mexico</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/t2F3C_cDn4MsCSxsjwOcwg.jpg"></icon><desc>Live coverage of the last round of fixtures in Group C as Saudi Arabia take on Mexico at the Lusail Stadium in Qatar. The Saudis beat Egypt in their final group game of 2018 but failed to reach the knockout stage having lost their first two matches. Frenchman Herve Renard has since been brought in as head coach, and he’s reinvigorated the Green Falcons. Mexico have endured a turbulent build-up to this tournament, with their manager ‘Tata’ Martino facing relentless criticism from both the fans and the national press, but a lot will be forgiven if he can guide El Tri to the quarter-finals after seven successive exits at the round of 16. Commentary is from Guy Mowbray and Danny Gabbidon.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130211000 +0000" stop="20221130221000 +0000" catchup-id="i__RqelLrXyo1gRHufUpbr01YVa7xpvtqKRPyQ11"><title>The Ice Cream Wars</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The inside story behind the investigation, trial and convictions that would lead to a 20-year battle for justice that gripped Scotland.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130221000 +0000" stop="20221130224000 +0000" catchup-id="S1tmtkzXJAjCqAKogXVasMcpFabzTmaosqAyxnR3"><title>Two Doors Down : Christine 69</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Beth and Eric are throwing Christine a 69th birthday party, but the celebration gets usurped by chat about a funeral, which leads Christine to start thinking about her own.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130224000 +0000" stop="20221130232500 +0000" catchup-id="COwxqV20Px_0I7gl3BXvyueFTpxEOsVNNDjhzoWS"><title>Newsnight</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bUQ-JbBOx1dTvpjQEinXPw.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Victoria Derbyshire.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130232500 +0000" stop="20221130235000 +0000" catchup-id="1T-diNKK1pbdcqflpPi6fSvx5FkRJ3iOm0yNSbK2"><title>Unspun World with John Simpson</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/CkI1Rc6kHuSpIQ4Wgt1MpA.jpg"></icon><desc>Unspun World provides an unvarnished version of the week's major global news stories - reliable, honest and essential viewing. The BBC's world affairs editor, John Simpson, brings his experience and expertise to bear on the most important international stories. In discussion with the BBC's unparalleled range of experts across the world, he uses their unique local knowledge to go beyond the headlines to get to the unspun truth about the world.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221130235000 +0000" stop="20221201015000 +0000" catchup-id="RAVlV9_B0bLZo41fbAWuzVWYgsTqoJQHd79GpiMI"><title>The Elephant Man</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/sBgbBwkEaYsSgx_-eiaQJw.jpg"></icon><desc>Moving drama based on the life of John Merrick, a man born in Victorian England with a disfiguring disease and apparently doomed to a grim existence as a sideshow freak until he is taken in and cared for by a London surgeon. Despite his dreadful experiences, Merrick is a gentle, intelligent soul and becomes a popular guest in society drawing rooms - but only if his deformed features are completely covered.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201015000 +0000" stop="20221201032000 +0000" catchup-id="0CC2COf3rlxPtSKHigLnHbzqYnaz-Jk-dz125CNC"><title>Signed: The People's Piazza: A History of Covent Garden</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>David Olusoga tells the story of London's Covent Garden Piazza. Helped by experts and eyewitnesses, he conjures up ghosts of the past - market traders, sex workers and activists.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201032000 +0000" stop="20221201064500 +0000" catchup-id="Cqz_9yWzpIIP2li2B92A5VfpCaA7CbiQhuNRFNj1"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201064500 +0000" stop="20221201071500 +0000" catchup-id="obCr7zSx7MFf_Fp5PsVCA_Bh-MXSiCRBeEYC_sT7"><title>Beechgrove Gardens in Winter</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>George Anderson and Calum Clunie round off the series of autumn and winter gardening advice from Beechgrove. They answer viewers’ questions on topics covering the gardening jobs that need to get done between now and the spring, and there is a report from father and daughter Erin and Joe Armstrong from their plot in East Lothian. Calum is back on his own plot at Beechgrove this week, planting bare root roses and moving a rhubarb crown, he also checks on the tatties he planted that should be ready for Christmas dinner. There’s also a report from another gorgeous garden that the show featured during the summer to find out what they are up to at this time of year.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201071500 +0000" stop="20221201080000 +0000" catchup-id="RxF-xo63mNf7uqSN6P1fUzUtpz5o5GF8IUT8F3dj"><title>Bargain Hunt : Newark 12</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/_n4I9rQNXfb1yt_rdabD_Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Christina Trevanion and the teams hunt for profitable antiques in Nottinghamshire with experts Thomas Forrester and Ochuko Ojiri before heading to Derby for today’s auction. Christina discovers how traditional letterpress printing is making a comeback.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201080000 +0000" stop="20221201083000 +0000" catchup-id="_nf6lF5aRGk4ghsB_iAfoZfxFgfr-KxcUbYwOsUV"><title>Signed: Iolo: A Wild Life</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/lYc5LyuYb1FV6U9KvNU8RA.jpg"></icon><desc>Iolo Williams goes back ten years to 800 ravens roosting in Newborough Forest, Anglesey and their extraordinary calls. He recalls a visit to Grassholme Island off the coast of Pembrokeshire in 1996 to see a colony of over 100,000 gannets. He also looks back at the wildlife of slate quarries, the breathtaking underground landscape of a mine in Blaenau Ffestiniog and a fantastic reef formed on a slate-boat wreck off the coast at Nefyn. Other gems include the parachuting displays of skylarks and rock pipits, and a couple of boat trips with fishermen in Cardigan Bay and the Dee estuary.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201083000 +0000" stop="20221201090000 +0000" catchup-id="r8unRFq2H1j_nfHM3Xc8FgPnTGwil2U4m2yg3Rju"><title>Signed: Between the Covers</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/8wf6Lq-RQXgwlOUeULrMyg.jpg"></icon><desc>Sara is joined by actor and author Ruth Jones, comedian and writer Kae Kurd, Harry Potter star and comedian Jessie Cave, and director and actor Samuel West. They share their favourite books and review this week’s two book club choices: the new book pick, The Second Sight of Zachary Cloudesley by Sean Lusk, and the selection from the Booker Prize backlist, Snap by Belinda Bauer.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201090000 +0000" stop="20221201100000 +0000" catchup-id="YITKfys9_gFJeolHJYMBliW8XDFlVjwONlTlRjWM"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/O4C25N7vCNk5hoXbwDrnIw.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest headlines, breaking news and sport from the BBC newsroom.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201100000 +0000" stop="20221201121500 +0000" catchup-id="W0H2mLv8MYEoO5jAN_due5Q2pUuQxx4A-snAjZdl"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/O4C25N7vCNk5hoXbwDrnIw.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201121500 +0000" stop="20221201130000 +0000" catchup-id="JnzSj_vSQ0d5jIWEp54Eu-6__oyns6WU-wFCpwa0"><title>Politics Live</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The big political issues of the day.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201130000 +0000" stop="20221201134500 +0000" catchup-id="kMgLj23trPCOZYfbRU-uF7__vVRjs7ACyai5tKB9"><title>Home Is Where the Art Is</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Nick Knowles challenges three talented artists to create beautiful artwork for people they've never met. Our arty trio must try to work out the buyer’s style and taste by snooping around their home, but when the two sides finally do meet, who will win the coveted commission? Today’s artists travel to Lancashire to a renovated worker’s cottage. The mystery buyer wants a gift for his wife and has a budget of £200, but will it be a wood sculptor, painter or ceramicist who makes the sale?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201134500 +0000" stop="20221201141500 +0000" catchup-id="lQ1c0CePhVam0qEyiNBKX2P8DUfJuCiMx2IKNZSY"><title>Eggheads</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/kxjywN32Sf7ZLWFid1pwVQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Jeremy Vine hosts the show where every day a new team of challengers take on probably the greatest quiz team in Britain. Can the challengers triumph or will the cash prize roll over to the next show?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201141500 +0000" stop="20221201144500 +0000" catchup-id="XOwIVUo3hY7H7BnlT22dyZ_Silpl5aKTZulNzovf"><title>Eggheads</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/kxjywN32Sf7ZLWFid1pwVQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Jeremy Vine hosts the show where every day a new team of challengers take on probably the greatest quiz team in Britain. Can the challengers triumph or will the cash prize roll over to the next show?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201144500 +0000" stop="20221201171500 +0000" catchup-id="np01KjEHXVEiwe0K0t0QECjmhJn7rqkHNLJPjnP6"><title>FIFA World Cup : Canada v Morocco</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/jNaJOX196IupOJmsRcBUXg.jpg"></icon><desc>Live coverage as Canada face Morocco in their final match in Group F at the World Cup in Qatar. Led by English manager John Herdman, the Canadians qualified for their first World Cup since 1986 in impressive style. Their team is packed with exciting youngsters, headlined by the brilliant Alphonso Davies, who has already won a host of honours including the Champions League for Bayern Munich. They and opponents Morocco faced a tough start, having already played Belgium and Croatia, so both sides will be targeting a win at Al Thumama Stadium to end the group stage on a high. Gabby Logan presents, with commentary from Robyn Cowen and Martin Keown.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201171500 +0000" stop="20221201180000 +0000" catchup-id="cZvpUI2ENyablQv-mVSerOQDTfcNb4MeZBX0-u0m"><title>Flog It! : Compilation</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc>In this special edition of Flog it! the programme travels up and down the county revisiting some of the historic venues from the series and bringing viewers brand new valuations and unexpected auctions. Paul Martin uncovers the fascinating stories of the people of Paxton House, past and present.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201180000 +0000" stop="20221201183000 +0000" catchup-id="AQiR4Nt-BzqZn0KXg4-S325YW-fp6M3QgKZIguje"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games : Week 13: Thursday</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/QTvvZ81udNlpPp2OS-TMAQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Every day this week, former winners Stephen Bailey, Charlie Brooks, Ria Lina and John Thomson take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Facing their second chance to win a prize, will the winning stars opt for the House of Games golden goblets, or will they be tempted with the must-have House of Games golden fondue set?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201183000 +0000" stop="20221201190000 +0000" catchup-id="boVOmnSbilof4fPx-fMt0gI35kWrHIPXqLnPuKsj"><title>Strictly It Takes Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/jBI3R8x1LdHWuBnckASH_A.jpg"></icon><desc>Janette Manrara dishes up more backstage gossip and behind-the-scenes action from the world of Strictly. Designer Vicky Gill gives an exclusive look at what the couples will be wearing for Musicals Week, and there's a first look at how the couples are getting on in training.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201190000 +0000" stop="20221201193000 +0000" catchup-id="1JeA0IcmmixU4J1yWoip73O6bHeK87VVYiameBGI"><title>The One Show</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/R8qfJ9w3gj4N7H0YuztRag.jpg"></icon><desc>Alex Jones and Ronan Keating with the stories that matter from across the country.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201193000 +0000" stop="20221201200000 +0000" catchup-id="O3VcaRYG7I3vGUS0xt2VkQ0dC44iiFNcV1ktHg23"><title>Nigella's Cook, Eat, Repeat</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/RNfKfE3Q5gek--wweFtreQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Once again, Nigella weaves her kitchen magic and shows how, with a little advanced planning and a minimal amount of effort, it is easy to produce delicious food. Nigella starts with a fluffy, white, no-knead bread, which she uses to sandwich her crispy fried chicken, accompanied by pickles and kimchi. Nigella then takes the fear out of making a fish stew, accompanied by a fragrant tomato base full of the warming flavours of mace, cinnamon and nutmeg. A daring dish of cherry flambe follows, using frozen cherries and kirsch, served up with her frozen cheesecake ice cream.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201200000 +0000" stop="20221201210000 +0000" catchup-id="dMCuvwzhIdpLDiaUlSzNmZflerBI6oikwO-vbZUw"><title>The Secret Genius of Modern Life : Electric Car</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Hannah Fry discovers why innovations in meat packing almost derailed the electric car revolution and how a breakthrough in camcorder batteries led to Elon Musk’s electric empire, as well as demonstrating how not to drive a multimillion dollar prototype car of the future.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201210000 +0000" stop="20221201215500 +0000" catchup-id="wrJQlpWmRqLPrWQW3CN7HSn9KwkUg1Kc3DWus3FA"><title>The English : The Wounded Wolf</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Fifteen years earlier, on Wyoming's Chalk River in 1875, Thomas Trafford arrives to establish his cattle ranch, along with his accountant and aide David Melmont. But events take a sour turn when Melmont becomes involved in a horrific crime, which ultimately has an immense impact on the lives of both Eli and Cornelia.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201215500 +0000" stop="20221201223000 +0000" catchup-id="jowFxEof56DxXizW-lIIWQ6IRJNMO5wDYaLgl3iE"><title>Live at the Apollo : Joe Lycett, Ivo Graham, Phil Wang</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/R2ZYBlQacXTt2yaq81nYYw.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201223000 +0000" stop="20221201231500 +0000" catchup-id="9UfjUdXwXshm-o0ANdgBcFyc89fwSJwIammQnSUz"><title>Newsnight</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bUQ-JbBOx1dTvpjQEinXPw.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Kirsty Wark.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221201231500 +0000" stop="20221202021000 +0000" catchup-id="3ugvjzpZLztW39JsILasHvW9ZDzZNz8l5QmVM9J5"><title>The Deer Hunter</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/vpqKADSKy2iY4eDdItvikg.jpg"></icon><desc>Powerful and poignant epic drama chronicling the experiences of three young steelworkers from a close-knit blue-collar community in Pennsylvania at the time of the Vietnam War, counterpointing their initial naive patriotism with the brutal realities they are forced to confront. Arguably one of the best anti-war films ever made, it won five Oscars, including Best Picture, Best Director and Best Supporting Actor.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221202021000 +0000" stop="20221202032500 +0000" catchup-id="oMDZ01BWRVnuxBicDa0tHdJK9Oxyyq8Q2hI2sfbl"><title>Signed: Strictly Come Dancing : Week 10</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/vseWTytrbafNTnrVWRtn4Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Strictly Come Dancing is approaching the last leg of the competition, and our couples have to do more than ever to secure their places in next week’s Musicals Special quarter-final. For the judges, expectations are high, so it will be another weekend of fantastic ballroom dancing.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221202032500 +0000" stop="20221202035500 +0000" catchup-id="hNxp0o_FktIw8qFzPI8UXcnunIHRSIebF2U5oNOS"><title>Signed: Strictly Come Dancing: The Results : Week 10 Results</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Tonight’s results show opens with another fabulous routine from our professional dancers, and special guests Tom Grennan and Joel Corry perform in the ballroom. Our couples can do no more. How have your votes at home changed Saturday night’s leaderboard? With a place in next week’s Musicals Special quarter-final up for grabs, the dance-off is not to be missed. Who will the judges save, and who will be your 2022 quarter-finalists?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221202035500 +0000" stop="20221202061500 +0000" catchup-id="M78bU0QnAeIGnFIrQQVmF_t5pDreMfPlRuEGkKzb"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221202061500 +0000" stop="20221202071500 +0000" catchup-id="tgx2yu3y-Joo4o-HnFjeoZmxYYfFZFHrfrrgnlIo"><title>Homes Under the Hammer</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/Honvrz_XaSQZKyAyWRd86w.jpg"></icon><desc>Jacqui heads to Lowestoft in Suffolk to see a one-bed flat that’s just a stone’s throw from the beach. Dion’s in the South Yorkshire town of Mexborough to visit a two-bed terrace in need of a full refurbishment. Tommy visits Whittlesey in Cambridgeshire to cast his eye over a three-bedroom detached house that is seriously lacking in kerb appeal.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221202071500 +0000" stop="20221202080000 +0000" catchup-id="9aIzKBTLovUv3BtC_5XAIFIyvjjk3PjClWYK55IL"><title>Bargain Hunt : Harrogate 6</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/_n4I9rQNXfb1yt_rdabD_Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Danny Sebastian heads to Harrogate, where experts Izzie Balmer and John Cameron help the teams identify profitable antiques before heading to Beverley Racecourse for today’s auction. Danny learns all about the Recycling Project.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221202080000 +0000" stop="20221202090000 +0000" catchup-id="ATpMcTXm8-m3GGYfc93MeYCSFWSSqvFtNiUE_nZ0"><title>Signed: Trawlermen: Hunting the Catch : The Race</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Karen of Ladram hunts for hake off Cornwall, a rookie crew work in the Irish Sea, trainee skipper Michael steps up in a storm, and Tydus heads out in search of crabs in the North Sea.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221202090000 +0000" stop="20221202100000 +0000" catchup-id="u3-gFTpzZPX6IZrFl8bzCNIdJ1GWbFYc14pZL24d"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/O4C25N7vCNk5hoXbwDrnIw.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest headlines, breaking news and sport from the BBC newsroom.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221202100000 +0000" stop="20221202121500 +0000" catchup-id="7SqsvjBNzGe9YPPvZ3w6mQBvRQdRhZXg_jpEvs4x"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/O4C25N7vCNk5hoXbwDrnIw.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221202121500 +0000" stop="20221202130000 +0000" catchup-id="yLk18BYWP30ew-3sANtpIddH9-s3l3tqcoFnhtxL"><title>Politics Live</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of the week’s proceedings at Westminster and the regional governments.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221202130000 +0000" stop="20221202142500 +0000" catchup-id="9w-FOsmzvCqMm2Sjcv063GM5JucmGtlth5Vu6sa6"><title>Heart of the Holidays</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/BREYGhT91SNqZNRlNKKg3w.jpg"></icon><desc>When her job transfer falls through, stockbroker Sam Wallace is forced to return home to upstate New York. Happy to be reconnecting with her mother for the Christmas holiday, she is less happy to be forced to confront her high-school sweetheart, whom she left to pursue her business career.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221202142500 +0000" stop="20221202144500 +0000" catchup-id="7AVGBC2p6dPNuXjcNeuVbdVFr9Qn_lt7F3SrUBqF"><title>Beechgrove Repotted</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>When garden space is limited, or just for the joy of growing your own, having an allotment is the perfect pastime. Starting in Calum’s allotment in Leven, we visit the other allotment holders in the Beechgrove team and see them through a whole growing season. At her allotment in Inverleith, Kirsty creates an allotment patch from scratch that is pretty, productive and purple. In Chris’ allotment, high in the Cotswolds, he and wife Frances take on an old disused plot and make it into a low-maintenance vegetable haven. And at his allotment in Joppa, George provides some of his top allotmenteering tips.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221202144500 +0000" stop="20221202171500 +0000" catchup-id="yYFKjgOsdwGGsJVCF0HBl8nUwQojXi1-8iCjHEUj"><title>FIFA World Cup : Ghana v Uruguay</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/ehzmsjam92aqs4jrPhD85Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Live coverage as Ghana take on Luis Suarez's Uruguay in a repeat of one of the most controversial fixtures in World Cup history. Their clash in the quarter-finals at the 2010 tournament has gone down in infamy. The Ghanaians seemed certain to become the first African side to reach the last four at a World Cup when Suarez stopped a goal on the line with his hands in the dying seconds of extra time. Asamoah Gyan missed the penalty and it went to spot kicks. Uruguay emerged victorious to leave Ghana both heartbroken and furious. Suarez is still playing, and as ever, is set to be the centre of attention as Group H concludes. Gabby Logan presents, while commentary comes from Steve Wilson and Dion Dublin.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221202171500 +0000" stop="20221202180000 +0000" catchup-id="R6hkcV7rY4Et7jSdiWq9B6Ma_DOGY9xOTtTYSqLD"><title>Flog It! : Nottingham</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc>Today Flog It! comes from the University of Nottingham. Antique experts Charles Hanson and Michael Baggott are on hand to find a selection of objects to take to auction. Charles comes across a rare 19th-century wax doll, and Michael is delighted by a 17th-century tortoiseshell box which ends up soaring in the saleroom. Paul Martin visits the Framework Knitters Museum in Ruddington where he learns how the 16th-century knitting frame revolutionised the knitting industry.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221202180000 +0000" stop="20221202183000 +0000" catchup-id="JuwivOlnPhHz01gnou3dyG1JIocp7eB0dsKoE-Mn"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games : Week 13: Friday</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/QTvvZ81udNlpPp2OS-TMAQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Every day this week, former winners Stephen Bailey, Charlie Brooks, Ria Lina and John Thomson take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Facing their second chance to win a prize, will the winning stars opt for the House of Games golden goblets, or will they be tempted with the must-have House of Games golden fondue set?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221202183000 +0000" stop="20221202193000 +0000" catchup-id="zA5enmvNHQeW_5xFXJABy8FZ94BLBT54ZuKEvLa2"><title>Strictly It Takes Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/jBI3R8x1LdHWuBnckASH_A.jpg"></icon><desc>Rylan is on hand with even more Strictly exclusives in this hour-long special and is joined by a trio of celebrity super fans. Also, there’s a sneak peak at the remaining couples’ rehearsals in the Strictly studio as they get ready for the Musicals Week extravaganza.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221202193000 +0000" stop="20221202200000 +0000" catchup-id="naHU-e9PWHg8m8HA1-G-avTLs5PEg1uYQ0QIpKHv"><title>The One Show</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/R8qfJ9w3gj4N7H0YuztRag.jpg"></icon><desc>Alex Jones and Roman Kemp with the stories that matter from across the country.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221202200000 +0000" stop="20221202210000 +0000" catchup-id="dKrizgBTexCXeiiqOz2FnRZ3u-SEENYsIOIILq-a"><title>Gardeners' World Winter Specials</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/Oa197OK--lZYNN1_PSH4Bw.jpg"></icon><desc>In the first of four special programmes celebrating the joy that the gardening year brings, Monty harvests his favourite winter veg, demonstrates how to take hardwood cuttings and plants up a container with tulips for a display of spring colour. Joe Swift meets TV presenter AJ Odudu and discovers her passion for houseplants, Carol Klein visits RHS Rosemoor in Devon, a garden with enough colour and texture to brighten even the darkest of winter days, and Sue Kent and Toby Buckland take an inspirational trip to Piet Oudolf’s garden at Hauser &amp; Wirth in Somerset. The head gardener at West Dean Gardens in West Sussex shares his tips on growing ranunculus, and there's a look at an incredible collection of bamboo at Trebah Garden in Cornwall. There’s also a chance to see what viewers have been getting up to in their gardens.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221202210000 +0000" stop="20221202220000 +0000" catchup-id="ISO4M9zgmxjm1rSUx4jtirZAI5WeX2nmuNm5_1Zt"><title>Agatha Christie: Lucy Worsley on the Mystery Queen : Destination Unknown</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>On the evening of 3 December 1926, Agatha Christie left her home in Sunningdale, Berkshire, in her Morris Cowley. The next morning, the car was found abandoned, balanced precariously on the edge of a quarry. Ten days later, Agatha was discovered in a hotel in Harrogate, claiming to have lost her memory. Lucy Worsley delves into this traumatic watershed moment in Agatha's life. She visits the key locations, from the chalk pit where Agatha crashed her car to Abney Hall, the grand house where she took refuge (and which would inspire several of her books). Lucy reveals connections between Agatha's real-life experiences and her novels, and uncovers new evidence about Agatha's mental health and the cutting-edge psychiatric treatment she went on to receive.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221202220000 +0000" stop="20221202223000 +0000" catchup-id="l9fvF2DXuiAVfH7E8mLm7nuQXC1lr5XEa_1_Hm92"><title>QI : Thrills &amp; Spills</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/mWzi8A0HiCWq5DjM2FsZkQ.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221202223000 +0000" stop="20221202230500 +0000" catchup-id="EHk7kv-xuxGjrYu5u046hDbszJ8YPrLMIzDBOFkn"><title>Newsnight</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bUQ-JbBOx1dTvpjQEinXPw.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Kirsty Wark.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221202230500 +0000" stop="20221202233500 +0000" catchup-id="eRoHYmmCbDeB4YCvReC1ynQEKzdT8yGEkbXNA4Ic"><title>How to with John Wilson : How to Invest in Real Estate</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/VB6xGo-ETn3egkyLB_ilxg.jpg"></icon><desc>After renting the same apartment for years, John Wilson contemplates an unexpected opportunity to become a homeowner.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221202233500 +0000" stop="20221203000000 +0000" catchup-id="tcbmZa1cIdRzylhp16UtCbqrTfnsdgUSeZ6Y6dEG"><title>How to with John Wilson : How to Appreciate Wine</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/ORBUoRyowX1aE7KdXpHesw.jpg"></icon><desc>When confronted by the overwhelming and mysterious world of wine, John Wilson attempts to master his senses and make informed choices.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203000000 +0000" stop="20221203003500 +0000" catchup-id="Pj-LraaPi6sjWVD7BYz8G0sRj3vxFiLx0zR6p8z1"><title>Frankie Boyle's New World Order</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/Yt8fAoVbMGXYLN5kURdE1w.jpg"></icon><desc>Frankie Boyle returns to help make sense of this disconcerting time, tackling the biggest issues troubling the planet and making a string of bold and often outrageous statements, which he then picks apart with the help of Kiri Pritchard-McLean, Jamali Maddix, Susie McCabe and Christopher Macarthur-Boyd.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203003500 +0000" stop="20221203013500 +0000" catchup-id="ksymAiMThXlftYmuMctdv6G6LbovJWHHan2KVu_0"><title>Agatha Christie: Lucy Worsley on the Mystery Queen : Cat Among the Pigeons</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Lucy Worsley explores Agatha Christie’s haunted, unconventional early life to discover the origins of her talent for murder – and uncovers some carefully concealed secrets.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203013500 +0000" stop="20221203023500 +0000" catchup-id="IsIYwen0EKko3u038QrcKe5SLJaRbdoepfUClu7i"><title>Signed: The Secret Genius of Modern Life : Food Delivery App</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Hannah Fry tucks into the tech behind food delivery apps like Deliveroo and Just Eat, which are now used by 24 million people in the UK. Hannah meets the R&amp;D team behind food delivery titan Deliveroo, finds out how pensioners ordering Greggs revolutionised food delivery, and discovers how pizza made us fall in love with the internet in the 1990s.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203023500 +0000" stop="20221203030500 +0000" catchup-id="OgzcQDW-a7o-kKsyNneVIYzNFIVfnkpjHW7nuCoC"><title>Signed: Iolo: A Wild Life</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/lYc5LyuYb1FV6U9KvNU8RA.jpg"></icon><desc>Iolo Williams delves into the archives to see the fantastic wildlife that he has filmed in Wales during the past 25 years. In this final episode, he recalls one of his first appearances on TV back in 1996 in which he was looking for black grouse on Ruabon Mountain. He also remembers heading to Scotland in 2003 to film mating golden eagles. Also in the programme, badgers playing outside a sett in broad daylight, nesting hobbies, an insight into the inventiveness and intelligence of birds, and mushrooms called spongy bum - very good cooked in vodka and poured over ice cream.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203030500 +0000" stop="20221203035000 +0000" catchup-id="nkeaQJenSwpgljYiiySNRH8PHMAMcODGTRxUGGd1"><title>Signed: Louis Theroux Interviews : Bear Grylls</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Louis gets whisked away by adventurer and television presenter Bear Grylls to visit his private island, where he is staying for the summer with his wife Shara. Louis sits down with Bear in an attempt to understand the real man beneath the tough-guy exterior. He learns about Bear being taken to see self-help gurus as a child and his experience of boarding school. Louis accompanies Bear on trips to a Scout troop in south London and a marine reserve training camp. They also head to Devon, where Bear is guest of honour at his own family adventure festival.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203035000 +0000" stop="20221203064500 +0000" catchup-id="htiXwmchgFJEoi21cBBcJXD-d1JcQN2_epvYEedk"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203064500 +0000" stop="20221203065000 +0000" catchup-id="6btoLMwOVF_KUrr2DqPCiCEZUXUVfzjX9qol_3AE"><title>Love Monster : Sparkle and Shine Day</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/eKm0H4f3WgNb6qPfZoWS6w.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203065000 +0000" stop="20221203070500 +0000" catchup-id="7f9Ym6-w0SgTWdm-1VtQzH_oY1DUKz0Uu1gU6ZW_"><title>Go Jetters : Go Jet Academy: New Species</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/SrF6Oaf0TYcd3bBhYKWMPQ.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203070500 +0000" stop="20221203071500 +0000" catchup-id="7Jy_NzFHpwICIYaTfy-wve76Spw1_C7bYmrQJkDB"><title>Hey Duggee : The Pen Pal Badge</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/dWM3mqwwsrDn2FnEUt-hHQ.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203071500 +0000" stop="20221203072000 +0000" catchup-id="OE0P7F1KrKeRXc7ZjRWAH_ybfMsA6qzIfJClSEuZ"><title>Hey Duggee : The Big Day Out Badge</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/PiWPFRPO-JC2OoBBkP_J-w.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203072000 +0000" stop="20221203073000 +0000" catchup-id="hAwxUJWfoCyLl540GfqKThz-amF9KuxfrW0HUP4m"><title>Shaun the Sheep : Prize Porker</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/RPLVrrlRE3QfWUnQ7al7hg.jpg"></icon><desc>Shaun suspects foul play when Ben wins all the prizes at the country fair.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203073000 +0000" stop="20221203074000 +0000" catchup-id="SBfqLvD5M1JXeGO2a3uxaAWQC5rtdB8Jwey0BFJp"><title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher: Unleashed! : Cats vs Dogs</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/noe5FPR55Oj-c7ChfmUfYQ.jpg"></icon><desc>A pampered cat attempts to oust Gnasher from his gang to remove him from Dennis's life, but no one sees what is happening except for him.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203074000 +0000" stop="20221203075500 +0000" catchup-id="ct7a1O7gnYCX968LRm1jMYWnrr7ZChEpEIVcs_ix"><title>Ninja Express : By the Seaside</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/BwPpLoM8E9ZNNFeT5XDzHg.jpg"></icon><desc>When an exhausted mother orders a replacement for her daughter's lost cuddly toy, the Ninjas must travel to a seaside fairground and stand up to some delinquent dolphins.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203075500 +0000" stop="20221203081500 +0000" catchup-id="cAQM-Fiz0a9a3_4TGPz2Aat-03sN9hTxb10l6OYT"><title>The Deep : The Hole Truth</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/D8FQ7vRcvkO9KTeSeOLg2g.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203081500 +0000" stop="20221203083000 +0000" catchup-id="tuQOSc-YSeQZyEXcw2YiRKxwgMEL2_fElAFEX-YC"><title>Odd Squad : Odd Squad in the Shadows</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/LqVOlkr4n0WEoFGAN0E6rQ.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203083000 +0000" stop="20221203085000 +0000" catchup-id="MK-owSayZH5GRTXp4JaKa2stZIeIstyZDqu-8Rvn"><title>One Zoo Three : Fright Fest</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>It’s a Halloween spooktacular at the zoo as the animals receive some eerie delights. There are creepy pumpkins for the lions, but will the meerkats brave their haunted house?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203085000 +0000" stop="20221203090000 +0000" catchup-id="WfFwmIzDyP0TW50biz9uN1Y1bYXgPpXa72ROAnFG"><title>Newsround</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/HsG2NEk_PJ2ML7EYnugwRw.jpg"></icon><desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203090000 +0000" stop="20221203100000 +0000" catchup-id="y21AdIfj4krlgn0ySoQY5dtshtow2sZ0RRRYdOJ6"><title>Deadly Pole to Pole : Hawaii Carnivores</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/brWjMZQtEQf81sM5CUJ13w.jpg"></icon><desc>Steve Backshall journeys to the remote Hawaiian Islands in search of three very different deadly carnivores. After days of searching the open waters for the mighty oceanic whitetip shark, Steve eventually comes literally nose to nose with this fearsome predator. On land Steve finds a most surprising predator in the forest, a carnivorous caterpillar that captures unsuspecting insects with its lightning-fast strike, something that has to be seen in super slow motion to be believed. Back underwater Steve wants to find out just how much might is in a moray eel's bite. With a double set of jaws and piercing teeth, this true marine monster destroys the deadly bite gauge within seconds.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203100000 +0000" stop="20221203113000 +0000" catchup-id="fU8-UJ4jd8maBlpGBf6gp_3Gz--MrZPQLc7sIBx2"><title>Strange Magic</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/MZGCWob-_Cebx7s3_9X0SQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Animated musical which draws inspiration from Shakespeare's A Midsummer Night's Dream. The Dark Forest and the Fairy Kingdom are two contrasting landscapes which sit next to each other side by side. Separated by a border where a special flower grows, all manner of chaos erupts on both sides of the divide when the flower is used to create a powerful love potion</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203113000 +0000" stop="20221203120000 +0000" catchup-id="zMIwnRR1R--pK7ew5ZuEsj0iZmVyXd0K9jOWMwGm"><title>Mountain Vets</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/K-yjy3206vapTyHFRCQz8w.jpg"></icon><desc>Jennie treats a giant boil on a cow's backside, Julie comes face to face with a rare wild animal she's never seen before, and Terry performs emergency surgery on the farm.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203120000 +0000" stop="20221203130000 +0000" catchup-id="oqS-AetZ5sf5U6ZozbkW3heHT2DNn1McD02AGHU8"><title>Top of the Shop with Tom Kerridge : Meat</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Four food producers with fledgling businesses come to test out their products on the locals in Malhamdale. This time, meat producers fight it out for one place in the final.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203130000 +0000" stop="20221203140000 +0000" catchup-id="H_jpaFwH6xYzEfMwFW8amPwa3J0MYMsc3XhcamjI"><title>Britain's Secret Seas : The Bustling South</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Documentary series exploring the seas surrounding Great Britain. The team explores our busy southern seas, which are littered with wrecks.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203140000 +0000" stop="20221203155000 +0000" catchup-id="Pn0mvyrWsbbqgAe-ExEXM_1hpY5kx6K19x_apmxs"><title>Operation Crossbow</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/2y-2GHwfLi8ud-wZ_8fizw.jpg"></icon><desc>Second World War action adventure. As V1 flying bombs fall on London, a gallant team of daring Allied agents is hand-picked to infiltrate and destroy the German weapons research station at Peenemunde. Rumours are rife that the Germans' research has led them to develop a new rocket, the even deadlier V2.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203155000 +0000" stop="20221203165000 +0000" catchup-id="xEpYA4MZSUJn0nTotLtwSt9U3RiT5cCA4LN_-DUB"><title>Flog It! : Powderham 5</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc>In this edition of the antiques series, Paul Martin and experts Will Axon and Mark Stacey visit Powderham Castle in Devon. Members of the public bring their antiques to be viewed and valued, with an option to sell at auction. Items include a shotgun case that belonged to a First World War hero, a pristine collection of Dinky toys, a telescope that once belonged to the captain of a tall ship and a rare Watcombe clock. Paul Martin delves into the the history of Powderham, uncovering a scandal, and takes to the seas to explore Plymouth's maritime heritage.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203165000 +0000" stop="20221203183000 +0000" catchup-id="FVHfjhjuaOtb3lOmIZF75jYYtWKAK1IXoYYY7XiF"><title>Nativity!</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/xGp8DSmR9YmRgSIyJBNbDA.jpg"></icon><desc>A teacher is put in charge of his primary school's musical version of the Nativity. They are competing with a local posh school to be the best-reviewed show in town, but are put under even more pressure when the teacher brags that his ex-girlfriend, who is a Hollywood producer, is coming to watch the show and is thinking of turning it into a film. But he hasn't actually spoken to his ex in years.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203183000 +0000" stop="20221203193000 +0000" catchup-id="ff7uPjoWSIfb4NmVCnIFYU16AJNPSa9fVBYdGxR8"><title>The Secret Genius of Modern Life : Electric Car</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Hannah Fry discovers why innovations in meat packing almost derailed the electric car revolution and how a breakthrough in camcorder batteries led to Elon Musk’s electric empire, as well as demonstrating how not to drive a multimillion dollar prototype car of the future.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203193000 +0000" stop="20221203201500 +0000" catchup-id="W_XHf9uWKivr0beYKzXKnCPUIpOMJ1mm0iXUZbdb"><title>Expedition Rhino: The Search for the Last Northern White</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>An expedition team including wildlife cameraman Vianet Djenguet venture into war-torn South Sudan in the hope of rediscovering the extinct northern white rhino.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203201500 +0000" stop="20221203204500 +0000" catchup-id="tSZJeEjXLMGEtIcBDCbd60afk9WOH-3sx9nv9NXp"><title>Grand Tours of Scotland's Rivers : The Past Reimagined</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Paul Murton explores the upper reaches of the river Spey - Scotland's third longest river - from its source in the wilds of Badenoch to Broomhill, halfway down. He hears stories of clan chief Cluny Macpherson, who hid with his gold for nine years in an inaccessible cave. Heading to a hidden tributary, Paul discovers a secret aristocratic Victorian love nest located in a remote glen where the wilderness is returning. In Newtonmore, Paul sees traditional Highland houses that remind him of Hobbit dwellings, before he rides a steam train on a heritage railway that follows the river Spey.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203204500 +0000" stop="20221203211500 +0000" catchup-id="I03-LJfRsQkqLKoDEdvpkPNz7_g8FFZ0nFvBrcIg"><title>Dad's Army : Sergeant - Save My Boy</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/z0QYrPofPxn3UK2ZIsrzgg.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203211500 +0000" stop="20221203221000 +0000" catchup-id="u7YV5oU3tNVj7uuMe1JLAqoIy54aRFyOq8JCmn1J"><title>Don McLean and Friends in Concert</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>American Pie and Vincent made Don McLean universally known as a songwriter. In this, his first television special, he displays his talents as a performer. Supporting McLean are The Jordanaires, the first time Elvis Presley's original backing group appeared outside the USA, and Britain's first lady of jazz/rock, Elkie Brooks.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221203221000 +0000" stop="20221203231000 +0000" catchup-id="fUJ9seYe6kn3IkNrZ1ffQoBLOD1NVtbtVDXEhJpL"><title>Classic Albums : Don McLean: American Pie</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/gPOfXOMOYOlmo7Z9c4jOqg.jpg"></icon><desc>Series focusing on the albums that have influenced the course of music. This edition looks at Don McLean's album American Pie, crowned by its titular overture and the song Vincent.</desc><category></category></programme>